<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>transcription regulator on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/transcription-regulator/</link>
    <description>Recent content in transcription regulator on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/transcription-regulator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AaHD8</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaHD8 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Identify a homeodomain-leucine zipper (HD-ZIP) IV transcription factor, AaHD8, directly promoting the expression of AaHD1 for glandular trichome initiation in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaMYC2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaMYC2 Gene Name: MYC2 transcription factor 2 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: The jasmonate-responsive AaMYC2 transcription factor positively regulates artemisinin biosynthesis in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaWRKY17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01956s266050/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01956s266050/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Aannua01956S266050 Gene Symbol: AaWRKY17 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaWRKY17, a positive regulator of artemisinin biosynthesis, is involved in resistance to Pseudomonas syringae in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaYABBY5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaYABBY5 Gene Name: YABBY family transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Transcriptional regulation of flavonoid biosynthesis in Artemisia annua by AaYABBY5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcNAC1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/acnac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/acnac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AcNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: A dramatic decline in fruit citrate induced by mutagenesis of a NAC transcription factor, AcNAC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcNAC4</title>
      <link>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acnac4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acnac4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc08288 Gene Symbol: AcNAC4 Gene Name: Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AcNAC4 regulates the transcription of AcAAT10 by binding to and activating its promoter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BjCdR15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-juncea/bjcdr15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-juncea/bjcdr15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BjCdR15 Gene Name: BZIP transcription factor15 Genome: Species: Brassica juncea Functional Descriptions: The Brassica juncea BjCdR15, an ortholog of Arabidopsis TGA3, is a regulator of cadmium uptake, transport and accumulation in shoots and confers cadmium tolerance in transgenic plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bZIP68;ABI5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/bzip68abi5zmabf3zmbzip33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/bzip68abi5zmabf3zmbzip33/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb176680 Gene Symbol: bZIP68 ABI5 ZmABF3 ZmbZIP33 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 68 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaASR1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/caasr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/caasr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaASR1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaASR1 promotes salicylic acid- but represses jasmonic acid-dependent signaling to enhance the resistance of Capsicum annuum to bacterial wilt by modulating CabZIP63.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaHDZ15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cahdz15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cahdz15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaHDZ15 Gene Name: HD-Zip I TF 15 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CaHDZ15 promotes pepper basal thermotolerance by activating HEAT SHOCK FACTORA6a.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClERF4</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clerf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clerf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: ClERF4 Gene Name: ethylene-responsive transcription factor 4 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClERF4 in regulating watermelon rind hardness and implied that ethylene is a common regulator of fruit firmness in both climacteric and nonclimacteric fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmBBX8</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbbx8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbbx8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CmBBX8 Gene Name: the subgroup II B-box 8 Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmBES1</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbes1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbes1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CmBES1 Gene Name: BRI1-EMS-SUPPRESSOR 1 Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmBPE2</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbpe2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbpe2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;DN58070_c2_g1 Gene Symbol: CmBPE2 Gene Name: Chrysanthemum morifolium BIGPETAL2 Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmHY5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmhy5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmhy5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmHY5 Gene Name: ELONGATED HYPOCOTYL5 Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: CmHY5 functions in apigenin biosynthesis by regulating flavone synthase II expression in chrysanthemum flowers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRC</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/crc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/crc/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CMiso1.1chr10g0266651 Gene Symbol: CRC Gene Name: CRABS CLAW Genome: Melon (Charmono) v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrWRKY42</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/crwrky42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/crwrky42/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CrWRKY42 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 42 Genome: Species: Citrus clementina Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CrWRKY42 coregulates chlorophyll degradation and carotenoid biosynthesis in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSA</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g16810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g16810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g16810 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0274800 Gene Symbol: CSA Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAGL16</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g048150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g048150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G048150 Gene Symbol: CsAGL16 Gene Name: AGAMOUS-LIKE 16 Genome: Cucurbitaceae genome database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The AGAMOUS-LIKE 16–GENERAL REGULATORY FACTOR 1 module regulates axillary bud outgrowth via catabolism of abscisic acid in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbZIP44</title>
      <link>/genes/citrus_sinensis/csbzip44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrus_sinensis/csbzip44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g25230 Gene Symbol: CsbZIP44 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsbZIP44 is essential for ABA-mediated carotenoid biosynthesis in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsJAZ6</title>
      <link>/genes/camellia_sinensis/csjaz6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/camellia_sinensis/csjaz6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsJAZ6 Gene Name: Camellia sinensis JASMONATE-ZIM DOMAIN6 Genome: TeaPGDB V1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMADS5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmads5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmads5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMADS5 Gene Name: FRUITFULL sub-clade MADS 5 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A fruit ripening-associated transcription factor CsMADS5 positively regulates carotenoid biosynthesis in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsS40</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/css0010485.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/css0010485.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CSS0010485.1 Gene Symbol: CsS40 Gene Name: Camellia sinensis Senescnece 40 Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor CsS40 negatively regulates TCS1 expression and caffeine biosynthesis in connection to leaf senescence in Camellia sinensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsULT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/crocus-sativus/csult1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/crocus-sativus/csult1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsULT1 Gene Name: ultrapetala transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Crocus sativus Functional Descriptions: Identification, cloning and characterization of an ultrapetala transcription factor CsULT1 from Crocus: a novel regulator of apocarotenoid biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DcHB30</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/dianthus-caryophyllus/dca25151/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/dianthus-caryophyllus/dca25151/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Dca25151 Gene Symbol: DcHB30 Gene Name: homeobox30 Genome: Carnation Genome database (http://carnation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DcWRKY75</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/dianthus-caryophyllus/dca5929/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/dianthus-caryophyllus/dca5929/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Dca5929 Gene Symbol: DcWRKY75 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor75 Genome: Carnation Genome database (http://carnation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor2 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb2 wound-induced transcription factor of persimmon (Diospyros kaki Thunb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb4 Gene Name: Myb transcription factor4 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb4 Is a Myb Transcription Factor Involved in Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Persimmon Fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRIF</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g20700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g20700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_3g20700 Gene Symbol: FaRIF|FaNAC035 Gene Name: Ripening Inducing Factor Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The NAC transcription factor FaRIF|FaNAC035 controls fruit ripening in strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FcWRKY40</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FcWRKY40 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 40 Genome: Species: Citrus japonic Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor FcWRKY40 of Fortunella crassifolia functions positively in salt tolerance through modulation of ion homeostasis and proline biosynthesis by directly regulating SOS2 and P5CS1 homologs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FveMYB10</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22020/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_1g22020 Gene Symbol: FveMYB10 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 10 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The R2R3-MYB transcription factor FveMYB10 is a major regulator of anthocyanin pigmentation in the red fruits of strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FvMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_7g15060/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_7g15060/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_7g15060 Gene Symbol: FvMAPK3 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 3 Genome: Fragaria vesca ID (v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FvRIF</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_3g20700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_3g20700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_3g20700 Gene Symbol: FvRIF Gene Name: Ripening Inducing Factor Genome: Fragaria vesca Whole Genome v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhERF-IIb3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gherf-iib3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gherf-iib3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhERF-IIb3 Gene Name: cultivar Reba B50 ethylene-responsive transcription factor-IIb3 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhERF-IIb3 regulates the accumulation of jasmonate and leads to enhanced cotton resistance to blight diseas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhERF6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gherf6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gherf6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhERF6 Gene Name: ethylene response factor 6 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton Major Latex Protein 28 (GhMLP28) Functions as a Positive Regulator of the Ethylene Responsive Factor 6 (GhERF6) in Defense against Verticillium dahliae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhFSN1</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghfsn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghfsn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A12G1049 Gene Symbol: GhFSN1 Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMYB212</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.007g350500.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.007g350500.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gorai.007G350500.1 Gene Symbol: GhMYB212 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 212 Genome: Phytozome v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhPAS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d12g0607/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d12g0607/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D12G0607 Gene Symbol: GhPAS1 Gene Name: PAGODA1 SUPPRESSOR 1 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The bHLH transcription factor GhPAS1 mediates BR signaling to regulate plant development and architecture in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSOC1</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsoc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsoc1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: GhSOC1 Gene Name: Genome: cotton reference genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmABF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/glyma.10g071700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/glyma.10g071700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.10g071700 Gene Symbol: GmABF3 Gene Name: abscisic acid-responsive element-binding factor 3 Genome: Wm82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmCAL</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmcal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmcal/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gm.02G121600 Gene Symbol: GmCAL Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmCAL-silencing plants still conferred resistance to SC8 that might be owing to incomplete silencing of genes with lower expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmCAT1</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmcat1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmcat1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.14G223500 Gene Symbol: GmCAT1 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Upon binding to GmDPB, PsAvh113 decreased the transcription of the downstream gene GmCAT1, which acts as a positive regulator of plant immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmDPB</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmdpb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmdpb/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.01G228100 Gene Symbol: GmDPB Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Upon binding to GmDPB, PsAvh113 decreased the transcription of the downstream gene GmCAT1, which acts as a positive regulator of plant immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmST05</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmst05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmst05/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;SoyZH13_05G229200 Gene Symbol: GmST05 Gene Name: Seed Thickness on Chromosome 5 Genome: [Zhonghuang 13 (ZH13) reference genome](https://phytozome-next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSW16.1;SW16.1</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmsw16.1sw16.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmsw16.1sw16.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: GmSW16.1 SW16.1 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Differential SW16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmZF392</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmzf392/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmzf392/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.12G205700 Gene Symbol: GmZF392 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmZF392, a tandem CCCH zinc finger (TZF) protein which was identified in our previous RNA-seq analysis of seed-preferred transcription factors, was found to function as a positive regulator of lipid production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GWHTACFB001163</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/cswrky13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/cswrky13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsWRKY13 Gene Symbol: GWHTACFB001163 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsWRKY13 acts as a negative regulator of lignin biosynthesis in tea plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNAC005</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnac005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnac005/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvNAC005 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Barley plants over-expressing the NAC transcription factor gene HvNAC005 show stunting and delay in development combined with early senescence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWIN1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvWIN1 Gene Name: WAX INDUCER1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: WAX INDUCER1 (HvWIN1) transcription factor regulates free fatty acid biosynthetic genes to reinforce cuticle to resist Fusarium head blight in barley spikelets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ID1;ZmIDD5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/id1zmidd5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/id1zmidd5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb047750 Gene Symbol: ID1 ZmIDD5 Gene Name: indeterminate growth1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JrVHAG1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/juglans-regia/jrvhag1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/juglans-regia/jrvhag1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: JrVHAG1 Gene Name: vacuolar H+-ATPase G 1 Genome: Species: Juglans regia Functional Descriptions: JrVHAG1 is involved in plant abiotic strss response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjERF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljerf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljerf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjERF1 Gene Name: transcription factor AP2-EREBP Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: A Positive Regulatory Role for LjERF1 in the Nodulation Process Is Revealed by Systematic Analysis of Nodule-Associated Transcription Factors of Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LuWRKY36</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/linum-usitatissimum/lus10026409/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/linum-usitatissimum/lus10026409/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lus10026409 Gene Symbol: LuWRKY36 Gene Name: Genome: Linum usitatissimum genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaICE1 Gene Name: transcription factor ICE1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Banana fruit NAC transcription factor MaNAC1 is a direct target of MaICE1 and involved in cold stress through interacting with MaCBF1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBIM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000143208 Gene Symbol: MdBIM1 Gene Name: BES1-INTERACTING MYC-LIKE PROTEIN1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Brassinosteroid signaling regulator BIM1 (MdBIM1) integrates brassinolide and jasmonic acid signaling during cold tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBT2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/mdp0000643281/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/mdp0000643281/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000643281 Gene Symbol: MdBT2 Gene Name: BROAD-COMPLEX, TRAMTRACK AND BRIC A BRAC2 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: MdBT2 is a BTB protein that directly interacts with and stabilizes MdCOP1 by inhibiting self-ubiquitination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdKCS1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdkcs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdkcs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD01G1087400 Gene Symbol: MdKCS1 Gene Name: Malus domestica β-KETOACYL-COA SYNTHASE 1 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000237742 Gene Symbol: MdMAPK3 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 3 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Ethylene enhances MdMAPK3-mediated phosphorylation of MdNAC72 to promote apple fruit softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000259614 Gene Symbol: MdMYB1 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 1 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB1–1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdMYB1–1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The effect of promoter methylation on MdMYB1 expression determines the level of anthocyanin accumulation in skins of two non-red apple cultivars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB1–2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdMYB1–2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The effect of promoter methylation on MdMYB1 expression determines the level of anthocyanin accumulation in skins of two non-red apple cultivars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB10</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmyb10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdMYB10 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 10 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Efficient induction of anthocyanin biosynthesis in transient assays by MdMYB10 was dependent on the co-expression of two distinct bHLH proteins from apple, MdbHLH3 and MdbHLH33.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPHR1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md05g1189400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md05g1189400/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD05G1189400 Gene Symbol: MdPHR1 Gene Name: PHOSPHATE STARVATION RESPONSE1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: determined that MdPHR1 was essential for Pi deficiency-induced anthocyanin accumulation in apple (Malus × domestica).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPHR1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdphr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdphr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD05G1189400 Gene Symbol: MdPHR1 Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdRGL2a</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdrgl2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdrgl2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD09G1264800 Gene Symbol: MdRGL2a Gene Name: DELLA protein Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdTCP15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md13g1073500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md13g1073500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD13G1073500 Gene Symbol: MdTCP15 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Histone deacetylase MdHDA6 is an antagonist in regulation of transcription factor MdTCP15 to promote cold tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdWRKY75</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky75/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000123888 Gene Symbol: MdWRKY75 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 75 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdWRKY9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/mdwrky9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/mdwrky9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdWRKY9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The Ca2+-MdCRF4-MdWRKY9 module negatively affects apple fruit watercore formation by suppressing the transcription of MdSOT2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeHDZ14</title>
      <link>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mehdz14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mehdz14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Manes.01G242300 Gene Symbol: MeHDZ14 Gene Name: Genome: Manihot esculenta, v8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MhZAT10</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mhzat10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mhzat10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD08G1086500 Gene Symbol: MhZAT10 Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0002631 Gene Symbol: MtEFD Gene Name: Ethylene response Factor required for nodule Differentiation Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631mt0064_00055/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631mt0064_00055/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0002631;MT0064_00055 Gene Symbol: MtEFD Gene Name: Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MxHA2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-xiaojinensis/md08g1130200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-xiaojinensis/md08g1130200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD08G1130200 Gene Symbol: MxHA2 Gene Name: plasma membrane (PM) H+-ATPase Genome: Species: Malus xiaojinensis Functional Descriptions: MxMPK6-2-mediated phosphorylation enhances the response of apple rootstocks to Fe deficiency by activating PM H+-ATPase MxHA2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYC2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/myc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/myc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g076930 Gene Symbol: MYC2 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbMYB4L</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf03570Ctg037 Gene Symbol: NbMYB4L Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network(https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOR-like1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/nor-like1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/nor-like1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g063420 Gene Symbol: NOR-like1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMYBJS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmybjs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmybjs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMYBJS1 Gene Name: Methyl jasmonate induced MYB-related Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: A novel R2R3 MYB transcription factor NtMYBJS1 is a methyl jasmonate-dependent regulator of phenylpropanoid-conjugate biosynthesis in tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsAPX1;APXa</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g17690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g17690/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g17690 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0285700 Gene Symbol: OsAPX1 APXa Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMPK6;OsMPK4</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g38950/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g38950/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g38950 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0533600 Gene Symbol: OsMPK6 OsMPK4 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRING-1;OsATL38</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g52210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g52210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g52210 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0759400 Gene Symbol: OsRING-1 OsATL38 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWAK1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/os11g0690066/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/os11g0690066/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: None RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0690066 Gene Symbol: OsWAK1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWRKY13;WRKY13</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g54600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g54600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g54600 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0750100 Gene Symbol: OsWRKY13 WRKY13 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PacCYP707A2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/paccyp707a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/paccyp707a2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PacCYP707A2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus avium Functional Descriptions: PacCYP707A2 negatively regulates cherry fruit ripening while PacCYP707A1 mediates drought tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaMYB10</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/pamyb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/pamyb10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PaMYB10 Gene Name: MYB transcriptional regulator 10 Genome: Species: Prunus avium Functional Descriptions: The R2R3-MYB transcription factor PaMYB10 is involved in anthocyanin biosynthesis in apricots and determines red blushed skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhOBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Peaxi162Scf00285g00011 Gene Symbol: PhOBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network (https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpbZIP44</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppbzip44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppbzip44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PpbZIP44 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: A pear S1-bZIP transcription factor PpbZIP44 modulates carbohydrate metabolism, amino acid, and flavonoid accumulation in fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsMYB30</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/paeonia-suffruticosa/cluster_9455/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/paeonia-suffruticosa/cluster_9455/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cluster_9455 Gene Symbol: PsMYB30 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB Transcription Factor30 Genome: Species: Paeonia suffruticosa Functional Descriptions: Tree Peony R2R3-MYB Transcription Factor PsMYB30 Promotes Petal Blotch Formation by Activating the Transcription of the Anthocyanin Synthase Gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtRD26</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tomentosa/potri.001g404100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tomentosa/potri.001g404100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Potri.001G404100 Gene Symbol: PtRD26 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus tomentosa Functional Descriptions: An alternative splicing variant of PtRD26 delays leaf senescence by regulating multiple NAC transcription factors in Populus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pvtb1a</title>
      <link>/genes/panicum_virgatum/pvtb1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/panicum_virgatum/pvtb1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pavir.Ia00838/Pavir.9NG142700 Gene Symbol: Pvtb1a Gene Name: Genome: Panicum virgatum v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pvtb1b</title>
      <link>/genes/panicum_virgatum/pvtb1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/panicum_virgatum/pvtb1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pavir.Ib04362/Pavir.9KG031700 Gene Symbol: Pvtb1b Gene Name: Genome: Panicum virgatum v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLL3</title>
      <link>/genes/lactuca_sativa/rll3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/lactuca_sativa/rll3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: RLL3 Gene Name: Red Lettuce Leaves 3 Genome: Lsat_Salinas_v8 Species: Lactuca sativa Functional Descriptions: The characterization of multiple polymorphic genes in this study provides the necessary molecular resources for the rational breeding of lettuce cultivars with distinct levels of red pigments and green cultivars with high levels of health-promoting flavonoids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SbEhd1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sobic.001g227900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sobic.001g227900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sobic.001G227900 Gene Symbol: SbEhd1 Gene Name: EARLY HEADING DATE 1 Genome: Sorghum bicolor v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SbGhd7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sobic.006g004400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sobic.006g004400/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sobic.006G004400 Gene Symbol: SbGhd7 Gene Name: GRAIN NUMBER, PLANT HEIGHT AND HEADING DATE 7 Genome: Sorghum bicolor v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fvh4_7g28640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fvh4_7g28640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_7g28640 Gene Symbol: SL1 Gene Name: SIMPLE LEAF1 Genome: Species: Fragaria vesca Functional Descriptions: A GT-1 and PKc domain-containing transcription regulator SIMPLE LEAF1 (SL1) controls compound leaf development in woodland strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAN11</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slan11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slan11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlAN11 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA GLABRA 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato SlAN11 regulates flavonoid biosynthesis and seed dormancy by interaction with bHLH proteins but not with MYB proteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAP2a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/slap2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/slap2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlAP2a Gene Name: APETALA2 transcription factor Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: A tomato (Solanum lycopersicum) APETALA2/ERF gene, SlAP2a, is a negative regulator of fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAS2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slas2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slas2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g063140 Gene Symbol: SlAS2 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlBES1.8</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbes1.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbes1.8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc10g076390 Gene Symbol: SlBES1.8 Gene Name: Brassinazole-resistant 1 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlbHLH114</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbhlh114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbhlh114/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g077790 Gene Symbol: SlbHLH114 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlbHLH95</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g079050/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g079050/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc10g079050 Gene Symbol: SlbHLH95 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Identified the SlbHLH95 transcription factor as a negative regulator of trichome formation in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlbHLH96</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbhlh96/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbhlh96/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: SlbHLH96 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: A bHLH transcription factor, SlbHLH96, promotes drought tolerance in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlDOF9</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sldof9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sldof9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g090220 Gene Symbol: SlDOF9 Gene Name: DNA-binding with one zinc finger 9 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlERF.G3-like</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slerf.g3-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slerf.g3-like/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g077790 Gene Symbol: SlERF.G3-like Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlHB8</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g066500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g066500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc08g066500 Gene Symbol: SlHB8 Gene Name: HD-Zip III family transcription factor 8 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The SlHB8 acts as a negative regulator in tapetum development and pollen wall formation in Tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlJAF13</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljaf13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljaf13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g081140 Gene Symbol: SlJAF13 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlJAZ2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljaz2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljaz2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc12g009220 Gene Symbol: SlJAZ2 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlLOB1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sllob1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sllob1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g120910.2 Gene Symbol: SlLOB1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMADS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slmads1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slmads1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlMADS1 Gene Name: MADS-Box Transcription Factor 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: A Tomato MADS-Box Transcription Factor, SlMADS1, Acts as a Negative Regulator of Fruit Ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMYB7</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slmyb7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slmyb7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc01g111500.3.1 Gene Symbol: SlMYB7 Gene Name: Genome: reference tomato genome SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMYB75</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slmyb75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slmyb75/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc10g086250 Gene Symbol: SlMYB75 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMYC2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g076930/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g076930/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc08g076930 Gene Symbol: SlMYC2 Gene Name: transcription factor MYC2 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlMYC2, a master regulator of Jasmonic acid response, has been found to exhibit high expression levels in fruit and has been implicated in the regulation of fruit ripening and resistance to Botrytis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlNAP1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slnap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slnap1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc05g007770.2.1 Gene Symbol: SlNAP1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSPL13</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g015840/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g015840/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc05g015840 Gene Symbol: SlSPL13 Gene Name: SQUAMOSA PROMOTER BINDING PROTEIN LIKE 13 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: miR156a-targeted SBP-Box transcription factor SlSPL13 regulates inflorescence morphogenesis by directly activating SFT in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlTAF1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sltaf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sltaf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc06g060230 Gene Symbol: SlTAF1 Gene Name: Transcription Activation Factor 1 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlWRKY53</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwrky53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwrky53/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g008280 Gene Symbol: SlWRKY53 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmERF6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00020272/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00020272/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SMil_00020272 Gene Symbol: SmERF6 Gene Name: ethylene responsive factor 6 Genome: miltiorrhiza online information resource (http://bi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmMYB5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-melongena/smechr0800147/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-melongena/smechr0800147/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Smechr0800147 Gene Symbol: SmMYB5 Gene Name: MYB TF 5 Genome: eggplant genome website (http://eggplant-hq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmTGA5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00004488/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00004488/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SMil_00004488 Gene Symbol: SmTGA5 Gene Name: leucine zipper family transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The SmNPR4-SmTGA5 module regulates SA-mediated phenolic acid biosynthesis in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StABF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StABF1 Gene Name: ABRE binding factor1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StABF1, a stress-responsive bZIP transcription factor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StERF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sterf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sterf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StERF3 Gene Name: ERF-associated amphiphilic repression Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The Potato ERF Transcription Factor StERF3 Negatively Regulates Resistance to Phytophthora infestans and Salt Tolerance in Potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaARF15-A1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf15-a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf15-a1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS6A02G113000 Gene Symbol: TaARF15-A1 Gene Name: Auxin response factor 15 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaARF25-5A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5A02G038300 Gene Symbol: TaARF25-5A Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaARF25-5B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5B02G039800 Gene Symbol: TaARF25-5B Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaARF25-5D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taarf25-5d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5D02G045700 Gene Symbol: TaARF25-5D Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaBA1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taba1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taba1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS3D02G344600 Gene Symbol: TaBA1 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaEIL1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taeil1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taeil1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaEIL1 Gene Name: ETHYLENE INSENSITIVE3-LIKE1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: bread wheat ETHYLENE INSENSITIVE3-LIKE1 (TaEIL1), an ortholog of Arabidopsis (Arabidopsis thaliana) ETHYLENE INSENSITIVE3, negatively regulates bread wheat resistance against powdery mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMYB4-7D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamyb4-7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamyb4-7d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7D02G272400 Gene Symbol: TaMYB4-7D Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMYB44-D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamyb44-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamyb44-d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4D01G297900 Gene Symbol: TaMYB44-D Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 44 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaVRN1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tavrn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tavrn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5A02G391700 Gene Symbol: TaVRN1 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaZFP1B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tazfp1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tazfp1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaZFP1B Gene Name: C2H2 zinc finger protein Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of TaZFP1B stimulates plant growth and up-regulates different oxidative stress-responsive genes under well-watered conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAHOX1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/vahox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/vahox1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: VAHOX1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VqMYB154</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-quinquangularis/vit_11s0016g02780/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-quinquangularis/vit_11s0016g02780/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VIT_11s0016g02780 Gene Symbol: VqMYB154 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 154 Genome: Species: Vitis quinquangularis Functional Descriptions: VqMYB154 promotes polygene expression and enhances resistance to pathogens in Chinese wild grapevine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvABF2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vtt_180001g10450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vtt_180001g10450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VTT_180001g10450 Gene Symbol: VvABF2 Gene Name: ABSCISIC ACID RESPONSE ELEMENT-BINDING FACTOR2 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: The Basic Leucine Zipper Transcription Factor ABSCISIC ACID RESPONSE ELEMENT-BINDING FACTOR2 (VvABF2) Is an Important Transcriptional Regulator of Abscisic Acid-Dependent Grape Berry Ripening Processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvibZIPC22</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_07s0005g01450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_07s0005g01450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VIT_07s0005g01450 Gene Symbol: VvibZIPC22 Gene Name: Pinot Noir basic region/leucine zipper motif C22 protein Genome: 12Xv1 assembly of the Pinot Noir genome(http://genomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VviNAC60</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_08s0007g07670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_08s0007g07670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VIT_08s0007g07670 Gene Symbol: VviNAC60 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 60 Genome: 12X.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvWRKY46</title>
      <link>/genes/vitis_vinifera/vvwrky46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/vitis_vinifera/vvwrky46/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;VIT_215s0046g01140 Gene Symbol: VvWRKY46 Gene Name: Genome: V.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIP1</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/wip1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/wip1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CMiso1.1chr05g0123221 Gene Symbol: WIP1 Gene Name: Genome: Melon (Charmono) v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woolly</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/woolly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/woolly/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g080260 Gene Symbol: Woolly Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZFP245</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g39970/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g39970/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g39970 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0588700 Gene Symbol: ZFP245 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAL14</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb353930/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb353930/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb353930 Gene Symbol: ZmAL14|ZmAL9 Gene Name: Alfin-like-transcription factor 9 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmbZIP111</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb031210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb031210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb031210 Gene Symbol: ZmbZIP111 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 111 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmbZIP4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb255970 Gene Symbol: ZmbZIP4 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmFDL1;myb94</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmfdl1myb94myb36fdl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmfdl1myb94myb36fdl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb328280 Gene Symbol: ZmFDL1 myb94 Myb36 fdl1 Gene Name: fused leaves1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGRAS11;scl1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmgras11scl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmgras11scl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb344400 Gene Symbol: ZmGRAS11 scl1 Gene Name: scarecrow-like1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmIBH1-1;ibh1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmibh1-1ibh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmibh1-1ibh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb067570 Gene Symbol: ZmIBH1-1 ibh1 Gene Name: increased leaf inclination1-binding bhlh 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmICE1;ICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1ice1zmiceazmscrambhlh175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1ice1zmiceazmscrambhlh175/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb142500 Gene Symbol: ZmICE1 ICE1 ZmICEa ZmSCRAM bhlh175 Gene Name: INDUCER OF CBF EXPRESSION 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmIDD5;id1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmidd5id1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmidd5id1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb047750 Gene Symbol: ZmIDD5 id1 Gene Name: indeterminate growth1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmILI1;ili1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmili1ili1qla2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmili1ili1qla2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb068900 Gene Symbol: ZmILI1 ili1 qLA2 Gene Name: increased leaf inclination1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmILI1;ZmbHLH197</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmili1zmbhlh197/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmili1zmbhlh197/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb068900 Gene Symbol: ZmILI1 ZmbHLH197 Gene Name: increased leaf inclination1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmLA1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmla1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmla1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb169480 Gene Symbol: ZmLA1 Gene Name: lazy plant1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmLRL5;lrl5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmlrl5lrl5bhlh10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmlrl5lrl5bhlh10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb374700 Gene Symbol: ZmLRL5 lrl5 bhlh10 Gene Name: bHLH-transcription factor 10 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMADS1a;ZmMADS2;ZAG2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmmads1azmmads2zag2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmmads1azmmads2zag2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb138380 Gene Symbol: ZmMADS1a ZmMADS2 zag2 Gene Name: Zea AGAMOUS homolog2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMKK4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb257340 Gene Symbol: ZmMKK4 Gene Name: MAP kinase kinase4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMM1;glk28</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmmm1glk28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmmm1glk28/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb298990 Gene Symbol: ZmMM1 glk28 Gene Name: Mexicana lesion mimic 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNF-YA1;nfya1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya1nfya1ca2p11zmnfya01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya1nfya1ca2p11zmnfya01/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb005690 Gene Symbol: ZmNF-YA1 nfya1 ca2p11 ZmNFYA01 Gene Name: nuclear transcription factor y subunit a1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNF-YA8;ZmNFYA15</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya8zmnfya15zmnf-ya4zmnf-ya13zmnf-ya14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya8zmnfya15zmnf-ya4zmnf-ya13zmnf-ya14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb327230 Gene Symbol: ZmNF-YA8 ZmNFYA15 ZmNF-YA4 ZmNF-YA13 ZmNF-YA14 Gene Name: NUCLEAR FACTOR YA8 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmPTF1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmptf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmptf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GRMZM2G024530 Gene Symbol: ZmPTF1 Gene Name: Pi starvation-induced transcription factor1 Genome: B73_RefGen_v3 Species: Zea mays Functional Descriptions: ZmPTF1, a phosphate starvation-induced basic helix-loop-helix (bHLH) transcription factor, contributes to root development and low-phosphate tolerance in maize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmTCRR-1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmtcrr-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmtcrr-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: ZmTCRR-1 Gene Name: transfer cell response regulator-1 Genome: Species: Zea mays Functional Descriptions: The maize transfer cell-specific type-A response regulator ZmTCRR-1 appears to be involved in intercellular signalling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmWRKY79;wrky79</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmwrky79wrky79wrky53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmwrky79wrky79wrky53/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb310270 Gene Symbol: ZmWRKY79 wrky79 WRKY53 Gene Name: WRKY-transcription factor 79 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
