<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ubiquitin e3 ligase on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/ubiquitin-e3-ligase/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ubiquitin e3 ligase on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/ubiquitin-e3-ligase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FaBRIZ</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/maker-fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/maker-fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: maker-Fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20 Gene Symbol: FaBRIZ Gene Name: RING-type E3 ligase Genome: Camarosa Genome Assembly v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhXB38D</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghxb38d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghxb38d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D09G1474 Gene Symbol: GhXB38D Gene Name: Genome: reference genome sequence for G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmCOP1b</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmcop1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmcop1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.14G049700 Gene Symbol: GmCOP1b Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: E3 ubiquitin ligase GmCOP1b negatively regulates the accumulation of soybean isoflavones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPUB21</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmpub21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmpub21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.02G242900 Gene Symbol: GmPUB21 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: We conclude that GmPUB21 and GmDi19-5 collaborate to regulate drought and salinity tolerance via an ABA-dependent pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaRZF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma02_p05740/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma02_p05740/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma02_p05740 Gene Symbol: MaRZF1 Gene Name: RING Zinc Finger 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: RING-type ubiquitin E3 ligase MaRZF1 interacts with chlorophyll catabolic enzyme MaSGR1, which promotes the ubiquitination and proteasomal degradation of MaSGR1, causing the green ripening of banana fruit under high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaSGR1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaSGR1 Gene Name: STAY-GREEN 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: RING-type ubiquitin E3 ligase MaRZF1 interacts with chlorophyll catabolic enzyme MaSGR1, which promotes the ubiquitination and proteasomal degradation of MaSGR1, causing the green ripening of banana fruit under high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBEL7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbel7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbel7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdBEL7 Gene Name: BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 7 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: An apple (Malus domestica) BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 7 (MdBEL7), potentially functioning as a transcriptional repressor of the Chl catabolic genes (CCGs), including MdCLH, MdPPH2 and MdRCCR2, was identified as a partner of the ethylene-activated U-box type E3 ubiquitin ligase MdPUB24 in a yeast library screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBIM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000143208 Gene Symbol: MdBIM1 Gene Name: BES1-INTERACTING MYC-LIKE PROTEIN1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Brassinosteroid signaling regulator BIM1 (MdBIM1) integrates brassinolide and jasmonic acid signaling during cold tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdCRF4</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdcrf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdcrf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MdCRF4 Gene Name: Malus domestica CYTOKININ RESPONSE FACTOR4 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000662999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000662999/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000662999 Gene Symbol: MdICE1 Gene Name: MYC-type bHLH transcription factor ICE1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Further study showed that MdPUB23 directly interacted with MdICE1, promoting the ubiquitination-mediated degradation of the MdICE1 protein through the 26S-proteasome pathway and reducing the MdICE1-improved cold-stress tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000237742 Gene Symbol: MdMAPK3 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 3 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Ethylene enhances MdMAPK3-mediated phosphorylation of MdNAC72 to promote apple fruit softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000259614 Gene Symbol: MdMYB1 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 1 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB308L</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb308l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb308l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000950559 Gene Symbol: MdMYB308L Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdNAC72</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdnac72/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdnac72/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdNAC72 Gene Name: transcription factor NAM-ATAF1/2-CUC2 72 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor NAM-ATAF1/2-CUC2 72 (MdNAC72), which functions as a transcriptional repressor of the cell wall degradation-related gene POLYGALACTURONASE1 (MdPG1).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPHR1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdphr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdphr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD05G1189400 Gene Symbol: MdPHR1 Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPUB23</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md14g1040300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md14g1040300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD14G1040300 Gene Symbol: MdPUB23 Gene Name: U-box-type E3 ubiquitin ligase Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Apple U-box-type E3 ubiquitin ligase MdPUB23 reduces cold-stress tolerance by degrading the cold-stress regulatory protein MdICE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPUB24</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdpub24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdpub24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdPUB24 Gene Name: U-box type E3 ubiquitin ligase Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-activated MdPUB24 mediates ubiquitination of MdBEL7 to promote chlorophyll degradation in apple fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPUB29</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdpub29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdpub29/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000194473 MD01G1010900 Gene Symbol: MdPUB29 Gene Name: U-box E3 ubiquitin ligase Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSCE1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsce1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsce1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD15G1286800 Gene Symbol: MdSCE1 Gene Name: Malus domestica SUMO E2 CONJUGATING ENZYME 1 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSINA1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1082000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1082000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD01G1082000 Gene Symbol: MdSINA1 Gene Name: E3 ubiquitin ligase 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdRGL2a and MdCIPK20 were ubiquitinated and degraded by E3 ubiquitin ligases MdSINA1 and MdSINA2, respectively, both of which were activated in the presence of GA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSINA3</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsina3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsina3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD02G1290000 Gene Symbol: MdSINA3 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSIZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsiz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdsiz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD11G1131700 Gene Symbol: MdSIZ1 Gene Name: SAP AND MIZ1 DOMAIN CONTAINING LIGASE1 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdWRKY75</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky75/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000123888 Gene Symbol: MdWRKY75 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 75 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdXBAT31</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdxbat31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdxbat31/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MdXBAT31 Gene Name: MdXB3 ORTHOLOG 1 IN ARABIDOPSIS THALIANA Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODD</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g11550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g11550/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g11550 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0214200 Gene Symbol: MODD Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCdc27B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcdc27b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcdc27b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCdc27B Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCdc27B1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCdc27B1 Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCdc27B2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCdc27B2 Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtRFP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrfp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrfp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtRFP1 Gene Name: RING-finger protein 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco RING E3 Ligase NtRFP1 Mediates Ubiquitination and Proteasomal Degradation of a Geminivirus-Encoded βC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPUB44</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g36360/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g36360/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g36360 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0439400 Gene Symbol: OsPUB44 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbATL18</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulifolia/pbr007980.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulifolia/pbr007980.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pbr007980.1 Gene Symbol: PbATL18 Gene Name: E3 ubiquitin ligase Genome: Species: Pyrus betulifolia Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor PbbZIP4 is targeted for proteasome-mediated degradation by the ubiquitin ligase PbATL18 to influence pear&amp;rsquo;s resistance to Colletotrichum fructicola by regulating the expression of PbNPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbbZIP4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulifolia/gwhpaayt014255/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulifolia/gwhpaayt014255/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GWHPAAYT014255 Gene Symbol: PbbZIP4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus betulifolia Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor PbbZIP4 is targeted for proteasome-mediated degradation by the ubiquitin ligase PbATL18 to influence pear&amp;rsquo;s resistance to Colletotrichum fructicola by regulating the expression of PbNPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGD1</title>
      <link>/genes/setaria_italica/sgd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/setaria_italica/sgd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Seita.9G123200 Gene Symbol: SGD1 Gene Name: small grain and dwarf1 Genome: Setaria italica v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGW2L-7A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7A02G151900 Gene Symbol: TaGW2L-7A Gene Name: GW2-like RING finger E3 ligase Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGW2L-7B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7B02G010000 Gene Symbol: TaGW2L-7B Gene Name: GW2-like RING finger E3 ligase Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGW2L-7D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagw2l-7d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7D02G107500 Gene Symbol: TaGW2L-7D Gene Name: GW2-like RING finger E3 ligase Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSDIR1-4A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasdir1-4a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasdir1-4a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: TaSDIR1-4A Gene Name: Salt and drought-induced RING finger1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMPK20;mpk13</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmmpk20mpk13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmmpk20mpk13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb297110 Gene Symbol: ZmMPK20 mpk13 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 20 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRFWD3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrfwd3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrfwd3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb000650 Gene Symbol: ZmRFWD3 Gene Name: ring finger and WD40 repeat3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRIN2;cl34141_1b</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrin2cl34141_1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrin2cl34141_1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb105020 Gene Symbol: ZmRIN2 cl34141_1b Gene Name: E3 ubiquitin ligase RPM1 INTERACTING PROTEIN 2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
