<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>virus on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/virus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in virus on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/virus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AcTPR2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach25g228601.2-ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach25g228601.2-ta/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ach25g228601.2-TA Gene Symbol: AcTPR2 Gene Name: TOPLESS-RELATED 2 Genome: (Ach25g228601.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGO2a</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/solyc02g069260/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/solyc02g069260/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g069260 Gene Symbol: AGO2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: AGO2a but not AGO2b mediates antiviral defense against infection of wild-type cucumber mosaic virus in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGO2b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g069270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g069270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g069270 Gene Symbol: AGO2b Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: AGO2a but not AGO2b mediates antiviral defense against infection of wild-type cucumber mosaic virus in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BcNAC056</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/bcnac056/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/bcnac056/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BcNAC056 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Brassica rapa Functional Descriptions: BcNAC056-GFP was located in the nucleus at the subcellular level, and BcNAC056 was responsive to leaf senescence and different hormones at the transcriptional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrCCA1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-rapa/bra004503/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-rapa/bra004503/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bra004503 Gene Symbol: BrCCA1 Gene Name: CIRCADIAN AND CLOCK ASSOCIATED 1 Genome: Species: Brassica rapa Functional Descriptions: Vernalization-mediated demethylation of BrCKA2 (casein kinase II α-subunit) and BrCKB4 (casein kinase II β-subunit) shorten the period of the clock gene BrCCA1 (circadian clock associated 1) in Brassica rapa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrMAPK15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-rapa/bra003834/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-rapa/bra003834/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bra003834 Gene Symbol: BrMAPK15 Gene Name: Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase 15 Genome: Brassica database (http://brassicadb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaAIL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca12g04370/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca12g04370/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ca12g04370 Gene Symbol: CaAIL1 Gene Name: AP2 transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaAIL1 Acts Positively in Pepper Immunity against Ralstonia solanacearum by Repressing Negative Regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaC3H14</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cac3h14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cac3h14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaC3H14 Gene Name: zinc finger CCCH domain-containing protein 14 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaC3H14 encoding a tandem CCCH zinc finger protein is directly targeted by CaWRKY40 and positively regulates the response of pepper to inoculation by Ralstonia solanacearum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaCKR5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca02g17820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca02g17820/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CA02g17820 Gene Symbol: CaCKR5 Gene Name: cysteine-rich receptor-like protein kinase Genome: cultivar CM334 genome Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: A cysteine-rich receptor-like protein kinase CaCKR5 modulates immune response against Ralstonia solanacearum infection in pepper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaERF28</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana02g000700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana02g000700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana02g000700 Gene Symbol: CaERF28 Gene Name: ethylene-responsive factor 28 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: A single transcript CRISPR/Cas9 mediated mutagenesis of CaERF28 confers anthracnose resistance in chilli pepper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaHsp26.5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annum/cahsp26.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annum/cahsp26.5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaHsp26.5 Gene Name: HEAT SHOCK PROTEIN 26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaLecRK-S.5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca04g04250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca04g04250/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CA04g04250 Gene Symbol: CaLecRK-S.5 Gene Name: lectin receptor kinase Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaLecRK-S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaLOX2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g000103/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g000103/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana03g000103 Gene Symbol: CaLOX2 Gene Name: lipoxygenase 2 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Involvement of sweet pepper CaLOX2 in jasmonate-dependent induced defence against Western flower thrips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaMYB12-like</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca05g18430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/ca05g18430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ca05g18430 Gene Symbol: CaMYB12-like Gene Name: Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaMYB12-like underlies a major QTL for flavonoid content in pepper (Capsicum annuum) fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capana10g000198</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana10g000198/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana10g000198/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana10g000198 Gene Symbol: Capana10g000198 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Gene expression and structure variation analyses indicate the Capana10g000198, encoding a R2R3-MYB transcription factor, is the best candidate gene for the msc-3 locus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaPMEI1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capmei1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capmei1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaPMEI1 Gene Name: pectin methlyesterase inhibitor protein 1 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Pepper pectin methylesterase inhibitor protein CaPMEI1 is required for antifungal activity, basal disease resistance and abiotic stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaWRKY1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cawrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cawrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaWRKY1 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor1 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Capsicum annuum WRKY protein CaWRKY1 is a negative regulator of pathogen defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaWRKY6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cawrky6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/cawrky6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaWRKY6 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 6 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: CaWRKY6 transcriptionally activates CaWRKY40, regulates Ralstonia solanacearum resistance, and confers high-temperature and high-humidity tolerance in pepper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcOMT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-clementina/czg_jg17822/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-clementina/czg_jg17822/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CZG_jg17822 Gene Symbol: CcOMT1 Gene Name: O-methyltransferase Genome: Species: Citrus reticulata Functional Descriptions: Using multi-omics resources, we discover a putative caffeic acid O-methyltransferase (CcOMT1) that can transfer a methyl group to the 3-hydroxyl of natsudaidain to form 3,5,6,7,8,3’,4’-heptamethoxyflavone (HPMF).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cm-eIF4E</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/cm-eif4e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/cm-eif4e/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Cm-eIF4E Gene Name: eukaryotic translation initiation factor 4E Genome: Species: Cucumis melo Functional Descriptions: Melon RNA interference (RNAi) lines silenced for Cm-eIF4E show broad virus resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmVPS41</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/melo3c004827/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/melo3c004827/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MELO3C004827 Gene Symbol: CmVPS41 Gene Name: acuolar protein sorting 41 Genome: Melonomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbHLH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa7g071650/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa7g071650/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa7G071650 Gene Symbol: CsbHLH1 Gene Name: Transcription factor BHLH1 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing analysis revealed that CsHOMEOBOX3 (CsHOX3) and CsbHLH1 are involved in nonglandular trichome elongation and glandular trichome formation, respectively, which corresponds with the transcriptome data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCCoAOMT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs8g05410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs8g05410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs8g05410 Gene Symbol: CsCCoAOMT1 Gene Name: caffeoyl-CoA O-methyltransferase 1 Genome: Citrus sinensis reference genome Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A multifunctional true caffeoyl coenzyme A O-methyltransferase (CsCCoAOMT1) enzyme participates in the biosynthesis of polymethoxylated flavones in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCER1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/camelina-sativa/csa6g079750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/camelina-sativa/csa6g079750/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa6G079750 Gene Symbol: CsCER1 Gene Name: ECERIFERUM1 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Camelina sativa Functional Descriptions: We identified 67 GT development–related genes, the functions of 7 of which were validated by virus-induced gene silencing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHOX3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g031750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g031750/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G031750 Gene Symbol: CsHOX3 Gene Name: CsHOMEOBOX3 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing analysis revealed that CsHOMEOBOX3 (CsHOX3) and CsbHLH1 are involved in nonglandular trichome elongation and glandular trichome formation, respectively, which corresponds with the transcriptome data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1a Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1a Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1b Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1b Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1c1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1c1 Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1c Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1c2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1c2 Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1c2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaOMT</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/faomt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/faomt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaOMT Gene Name: O-methyltransferase Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: It is methylated further by FaOMT (Fragaria×ananassa O-methyltransferase) to 2,5-dimethyl-4-methoxy-3(2H)-furanone (DMMF) during the ripening process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRIPK1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faripk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faripk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaRIPK1 Gene Name: red-initial protein kinase1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Silencing FaRIPK1 expression by VIGS affects ripening-related processes and corresponding gene expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FcWRKY40</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FcWRKY40 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 40 Genome: Species: Citrus japonic Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor FcWRKY40 of Fortunella crassifolia functions positively in salt tolerance through modulation of ion homeostasis and proline biosynthesis by directly regulating SOS2 and P5CS1 homologs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FvePHP</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_1g25470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_1g25470/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_1g25470 Gene Symbol: FvePHP Gene Name: Genome: F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gh_A04G0377;GhDNRs</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gh_a04g0377ghdnrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gh_a04g0377ghdnrs/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A04G0377 Gene Symbol: Gh_A04G0377 GhDNRs Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gh_A04G0378;GhDNRs</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gh_a04g0378ghdnrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gh_a04g0378ghdnrs/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A04G0378 Gene Symbol: Gh_A04G0378 GhDNRs Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhADF6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/gh_a09g0773/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/gh_a09g0773/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_A09G0773 Gene Symbol: GhADF6 Gene Name: actin depolymerizing factor 6 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: GhADF6-mediated actin reorganization is associated with defence against Verticillium dahliae infection in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhADF6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/gh_d09g0714/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/gh_d09g0714/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_D09G0714 Gene Symbol: GhADF6 Gene Name: actin depolymerizing factor 6 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: GhADF6-mediated actin reorganization is associated with defence against Verticillium dahliae infection in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhAPL</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d02g0291/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d02g0291/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D02G0291 Gene Symbol: GhAPL Gene Name: Genome: CottonFGD(https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCDPK28-A10</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcdpk28-a10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcdpk28-a10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A10G086300 Gene Symbol: GhCDPK28-A10 Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCKX14</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g1177/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g1177/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_D01G1177 Gene Symbol: GhCKX14 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCKX14 responding to drought stress by modulating antioxi-dative enzyme activity in Gossypium hirsutum compared to CKX family genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCNX6</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcnx6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcnx6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D09G2402.1 Gene Symbol: GhCNX6 Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a01g0621/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a01g0621/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A01G0621 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a04g0148/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a04g0148/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A04G0148 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a13g1164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a13g1164/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A13G1164 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g2360/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g2360/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D01G2360 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d05g3567/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d05g3567/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D05G3567 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK33</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d13g1455/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d13g1455/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D13G1455 Gene Symbol: GhCPK33 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhCPK33 Negatively Regulates Defense against Verticillium dahliae by Phosphorylating GhOPR3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhERF105</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a12g2166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a12g2166/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_A12G2166 Gene Symbol: GhERF105 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Silencing of GhERF105 reduced gland formation and gossypol biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhHAK5aA</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a01g1516/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a01g1516/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A01G1516 Gene Symbol: GhHAK5aA Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton High-Affinity K+ Transporter, GhHAK5a, Is Essential for Shoot Regulation of K+ Uptake in Root under Potassium Deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhHAK5aD</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g1760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d01g1760/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D01G1760 Gene Symbol: GhHAK5aD Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton High-Affinity K+ Transporter, GhHAK5a, Is Essential for Shoot Regulation of K+ Uptake in Root under Potassium Deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhLAC4-3</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghlac4-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghlac4-3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GH_D04G1418 Gene Symbol: GhLAC4-3 Gene Name: Genome: M-1 reference genome Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: These results suggest that GhLAC4-3 might enhance aphid resistance by regulating lignin biosynthesis in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhLYI</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghlyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghlyi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D08G0312 Gene Symbol: GhLYI Gene Name: LINT YIELD INCREASING Genome: eference genome of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMLP28</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmlp28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmlp28/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhMLP28 Gene Name: Major Latex Protein 28 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton Major Latex Protein 28 (GhMLP28) Functions as a Positive Regulator of the Ethylene Responsive Factor 6 (GhERF6) in Defense against Verticillium dahliae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMPK20</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmpk20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmpk20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhMPK20 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase 20 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The cotton MAPK kinase GhMPK20 negatively regulates resistance to Fusarium oxysporum by mediating the MKK4–MPK20–WRKY40 cascade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSAG20</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsag20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsag20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A06G1407 Gene Symbol: GhSAG20 Gene Name: Genome: reference genome of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSDG51</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d06g2123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d06g2123/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_D06G2123 Gene Symbol: GhSDG51 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Genome-wide analysis of SET domain genes and the function of GhSDG51 during salt stress in upland cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmERF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmerf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmerf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmERF3 Gene Name: EREBP/AP2 transcription factor Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of the soybean GmERF3 gene, an AP2/ERF type transcription factor for increased tolerances to salt, drought, and diseases in transgenic tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmHZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmhz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmhz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmHZ1 Gene Name: HDZip I protein Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmHZ1 was characterized by the presence of a homeodomain (HD) with a closely linked leucine zipper motif (Zip).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPAP2.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma06g028100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma06g028100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma06g028100 Gene Symbol: GmPAP2.1 Gene Name: purple acid phosphatase Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of purple acid phosphatase GmPAP2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRIN4a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g19920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g19920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma03g19920 Gene Symbol: GmRIN4a Gene Name: RPM1-interacting 4 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmRIN4 protein family members function nonredundantly in soybean race-specific resistance against Pseudomonas syringae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRIN4b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma16g12160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma16g12160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma16g12160 Gene Symbol: GmRIN4b Gene Name: RPM1-interacting 4 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Using virus-induced gene silencing, we show that only GmRIN4a and b are required for Rpg1-b-mediated resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRPA3a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma19g38100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma19g38100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma19g38100 Gene Symbol: GmRPA3a Gene Name: Replication Protein A subunit 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Replication protein A subunit 3 and the iron efficiency response in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRPA3b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g35460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g35460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma03g35460 Gene Symbol: GmRPA3b Gene Name: Replication Protein A subunit 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Replication protein A subunit 3 and the iron efficiency response in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRPA3c</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma20g24590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma20g24590/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma20g24590 Gene Symbol: GmRPA3c Gene Name: Replication Protein A subunit 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Replication protein A subunit 3 and the iron efficiency response in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRPA3d</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma10g42530/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma10g42530/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma10g42530 Gene Symbol: GmRPA3d Gene Name: Replication Protein A subunit 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Replication protein A subunit 3 and the iron efficiency response in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoSPGF</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gospgf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gospgf/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GH_D08G1984 Gene Symbol: GoSPGF Gene Name: Gossypium STEM PIGMENT GLAND FORMING GENE Genome: TM-1 reference genome Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The discovery of the novel stem pigment gland-forming gene GoSPGF by map-based cloning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoSTR</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gostr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gostr/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GH_D08G0109 Gene Symbol: GoSTR Gene Name: Gossypium Stem Trichome Repressor Genome: TM-1 reference genome Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GoSTR, a negative modulator of stem trichome formation in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvAKT2</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvakt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvakt2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvAKT2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of HvAKT2 and HvHAK1 enhanced K+ uptake and H+ homoeostasis leading to drought tolerance in these transgenic lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvEXPB7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvEXPB7 Gene Name: β-expansin gene Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvEXPB7, a novel β-expansin gene revealed by the root hair transcriptome of Tibetan wild barley, improves root hair growth under drought stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHAK1</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhak1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhak1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvHAK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of HvAKT2 and HvHAK1 enhanced K+ uptake and H+ homoeostasis leading to drought tolerance in these transgenic lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMPK4</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmpk4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmpk4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvMPK4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvMPK4 phosphorylates HvWRKY1 to enhance its suppression of barley immunity to powdery mildew fungus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPDS</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvpds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvpds/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU4Hr1G077450 Gene Symbol: HvPDS Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our previous study reported that knockdown of the barley phytoene desaturase gene HvPDS by virus-induced gene silencing resulted in a photobleaching phenotype in seedlings Agrobacterium-mediated transformation was performed on microspore-derived callus to target the HvPDS gene, and T0 albinos with targeted mutations were successfully obtained from commercial varieties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWIN1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvWIN1 Gene Name: WAX INDUCER1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: WAX INDUCER1 (HvWIN1) transcription factor regulates free fatty acid biosynthetic genes to reinforce cuticle to resist Fusarium head blight in barley spikelets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaTRE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0223881/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0223881/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lalb_Chr05g0223881 Gene Symbol: LaTRE1 Gene Name: TREHALASE1 Genome: Species: Lupinus albus Functional Descriptions: Under P deficiency, validamycin A treatment, which inhibits trehalase, led to the accumulation of trehalose and promoted the formation of CR with enhanced organic acid production, whereas overexpression of the white lupin TREHALASE1 (LaTRE1) led to decreased trehalose levels, lateral rootlet density, and organic acid production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeHB-1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g086930.3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g086930.3.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g086930.3.1 Gene Symbol: LeHB-1 Gene Name: Homeobox-leucine zipper protein Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: A tomato HD-Zip homeobox protein, LeHB-1, plays an important role in floral organogenesis and ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeHT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/leht1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/leht1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeHT1 Gene Name: hexose transporter 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Involvement of the Hexose Transporter Gene LeHT1 and of Sugars in Resistance of Tomato to Tomato Yellow Leaf Curl Virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LrABCF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LrABCF1 Gene Name: ATP-binding cassette transporter1 Genome: Species: Lilium regale Functional Descriptions: LrABCF1, a GCN-type ATP-binding cassette transporter from Lilium regale, is involved in defense responses against viral and fungal pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LrNAC35</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/unigene0012070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/unigene0012070/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Unigene0012070 Gene Symbol: LrNAC35 Gene Name: NAC domain-containing protein 35-like Genome: Species: Lilium regale Functional Descriptions: Ectopic overexpression of LrNAC35 alters flowering time in petunia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LsWRKY70</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lswrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lswrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LsWRKY70 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Lactuca sativa Functional Descriptions: GA signaling protein LsRGL1 interacts with the abscisic acid signaling-related gene LsWRKY70 to affect the bolting of leaf lettuce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSQS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsqs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsqs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdSQS1 Gene Name: squalene synthase 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of the two squalene synthase isoforms of apple tree (Malus × domestica L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSQS2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsqs2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsqs2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdSQS2 Gene Name: squalene synthase 2 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of the two squalene synthase isoforms of apple tree (Malus × domestica L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeTT8</title>
      <link>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mett8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mett8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Manes.01G208400 Gene Symbol: MeTT8 Gene Name: Genome: Manihot esculenta, v6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaMKK1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namkk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namkk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaMKK1 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase kinase 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: Two mitogen-activated protein kinase kinases, MKK1 and MEK2, are involved in wounding- and specialist lepidopteran herbivore Manduca sexta-induced responses in Nicotiana attenuata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaWRKY70</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nawrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nawrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaWRKY70 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 70 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: NaWRKY70 is a key regulator of Nicotiana attenuata resistance to Alternaria alternata through regulation of phytohormones and phytoalexins biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbALD1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf04547g02001.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf04547g02001.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf04547g02001.1 Gene Symbol: NbALD1 Gene Name: AGD2-LIKE DEFENCE RESPONSE PROTEIN 1 Genome: Nicotiana benthamiana Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbALY916</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbaly916/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbaly916/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbALY916 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbALY916 is involved in potato virus X P25-triggered cell death in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbBTF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbtf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbtf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbBTF3 Gene Name: basic transcription factor 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Silencing of NbBTF3 results in developmental defects and disturbed gene expression in chloroplasts and mitochondria of higher plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCML30</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf07608g00007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf07608g00007/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf07608g00007 Gene Symbol: NbCML30 Gene Name: calmodulin-like protein 30 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Tobacco mosaic virus hijacks its coat protein-interacting protein IP-L to inhibit NbCML30, a calmodulin-like protein, to enhance its infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCMT3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCMT3 Gene Name: chromomethylase protein 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of NbCMT3/3-2 in N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCMT3-2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCMT3-2 Gene Name: chromomethylase3-2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Developmental- and Tissue-Specific Expression of NbCMT3-2 Encoding a Chromomethylase in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbEXPA1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbs00007680g0013.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbs00007680g0013.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: NbS00007680g0013.1 Gene Symbol: NbEXPA1 Gene Name: α-expansin protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbEXPA1, an α-expansin, is plasmodesmata-specific and a novel host factor for potyviral infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbGSTU4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbgstu4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbgstu4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbGSTU4 Gene Name: glutathione transferase4 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: The glutathione transferase of Nicotiana benthamiana NbGSTU4 plays a role in regulating the early replication of Bamboo mosaic virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbMYB4L</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf03570Ctg037 Gene Symbol: NbMYB4L Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network(https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRabE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRabE1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: We characterized the gene expression, subcellular localization, and in vivo functions of a Nicotiana benthamiana small GTPase belonging to the RabE family, designated NbRabE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRABG3f</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabg3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabg3f/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRABG3f Gene Name: Rab small GTPase Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbRABG3f, a member of Rab GTPase, is involved in Bamboo mosaic virus infection in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRae1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrae1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrae1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRae1 Gene Name: RNA export 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of Nicotiana benthamiana Rae1, NbRae1, which encodes a protein with four WD40 repeats, resulted in growth arrest and abnormal leaf development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRAF2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbraf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbraf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRAF2 Gene Name: Rubisco assembly factor 2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Rubisco assembly factor 2 (NbRAF2), which localizes in the nucleus, cell periphery, chloroplasts, and stromules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOR-like1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/nor-like1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/nor-like1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g063420 Gene Symbol: NOR-like1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtRHO1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrho1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrho1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtRHO1 Gene Name: Rho-type GTPase 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The small GTPase NtRHO1 negatively regulates tobacco defense response to tobacco mosaic virus by interacting with NtWRKY50.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PacCYP707A1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/paccyp707a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/paccyp707a1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PacCYP707A1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus avium Functional Descriptions: PacCYP707A2 negatively regulates cherry fruit ripening while PacCYP707A1 mediates drought tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PavSCPL</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/pav_sc0000480.1_g920.1.mk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-avium/pav_sc0000480.1_g920.1.mk/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pav_sc0000480.1_g920.1.mk Gene Symbol: PavSCPL Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus avium Functional Descriptions: A 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbABCG1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-bellina/pbabcg1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-bellina/pbabcg1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbABCG1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Phalaenopsis bellina Functional Descriptions: PbABCG1 and PbABCG2 transporters are required for the emission of floral monoterpenes in Phalaenopsis bellina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbABCG2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-bellina/pbabcg2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-bellina/pbabcg2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbABCG2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Phalaenopsis bellina Functional Descriptions: PbABCG1 and PbABCG2 transporters are required for the emission of floral monoterpenes in Phalaenopsis bellina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrMYB21</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulaefolia/pbr028812.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulaefolia/pbr028812.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pbr028812.1 Gene Symbol: PbrMYB21 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 21 Genome: Species: Pyrus betulaefolia Functional Descriptions: PbrMYB21, a novel MYB protein of Pyrus betulaefolia, functions in drought tolerance and modulates polyamine levels by regulating arginine decarboxylase gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeDL2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-equestris/pedl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-equestris/pedl2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PeDL2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Phalaenopsis equestris Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing (VIGS) of PeDL1 and PeDL2 affected the number of protuberant ovule initials differentiated from the placenta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhERF2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pherf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pherf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhERF2 Gene Name: ethylene-responsive-element-binding factor 2 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: A petunia ethylene-responsive element binding factor, PhERF2, plays an important role in antiviral RNA silencing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhOBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Peaxi162Scf00285g00011 Gene Symbol: PhOBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network (https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhERF113</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf113/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhERF113 Gene Name: cultivar cultivar Samantha ERF113 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaa Functional Descriptions: RhERF113 Functions in Ethylene-Induced Petal Senescence by Modulating Cytokinin Content in Rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RsMYB1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/raphanus-sativus/rsmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/raphanus-sativus/rsmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RsMYB1 Gene Name: Bordeaux anthocyanin regulator Genome: Species: Raphanus sativus Functional Descriptions: Transposon-induced methylation of the RsMYB1 promoter disturbs anthocyanin accumulation in red-fleshed radish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl3-MMP</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl3-mmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl3-mmp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Sl3-MMP Gene Name: matrix metalloproteinase precursor Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato Sl3-MMP, a member of the Matrix metalloproteinase family, is required for disease resistance against Botrytis cinerea and Pseudomonas syringae pv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl5R-1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sl5r-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sl5r-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc05g009740 Gene Symbol: Sl5R-1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlGSTU38</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g011580.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g011580.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc09g011580.2 Gene Symbol: SlGSTU38 Gene Name: glutathione S-transferase 38 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato SlGSTU38 interacts with the PepMV coat protein and promotes viral infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlNAC1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slnac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slnac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of tomato SlNAC1transcription factor alters fruit pigmentation and softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlOSCA4.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g083430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g083430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g083430 Gene Symbol: SlOSCA4.1 Gene Name: calcium-permeable channel 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlOSCA4.1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slosca4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slosca4.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g083430 Gene Symbol: SlOSCA4.1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSKIP2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g092990.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g092990.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g092990.1 Gene Symbol: SlSKIP2 Gene Name: F-box protein SKIP2 Genome: S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlVQ15</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slvq15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slvq15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g043250 Gene Symbol: SlVQ15 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StCBL3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g013800.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g013800.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.06G013800.1 Gene Symbol: StCBL3 Gene Name: Calcineurin B-Like protein 3 Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StEXA1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.04g035210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.04g035210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.04G035210 Gene Symbol: StEXA1 Gene Name: Essential for potexvirus Accumulation 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Susceptibility factor StEXA1 interacts with StnCBP to facilitate potato virus Y accumulation through the stress granule-dependent RNA regulatory pathway in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StLTP6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StLTP6 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Potato (Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPBS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpbs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpbs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPBS1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Decoy engineering of the receptor-like cytoplasmic kinase StPBS1 to defend against virus infection in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPIP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400014879/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400014879/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400014879 Gene Symbol: StPIP1 Gene Name: Genome: Spud DB (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaAMT2</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taamt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taamt2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaAMT2|3a Gene Name: AMT2-type ammonium transporter Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaAMT2|3a|TaAMT2|3a, a wheat AMT2-type ammonium transporter, facilitates the infection of stripe rust fungus on wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaASR-3B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3b02g578200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3b02g578200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3B02G578200 Gene Symbol: TaASR-3B Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Pst21674 interaction with the abscisic acid-, stress-, and ripening-induced protein TaASR3 was validated mainly in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaASR-3D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3d02g517100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3d02g517100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3D02G517100 Gene Symbol: TaASR-3D Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Pst21674 interaction with the abscisic acid-, stress-, and ripening-induced protein TaASR3 was validated mainly in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaASR3-A1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g510100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g510100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3A02G510100 Gene Symbol: TaASR3-A1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Pst21674 interaction with the abscisic acid-, stress-, and ripening-induced protein TaASR3 was validated mainly in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaASR3-A2</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g510200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g510200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3A02G510200 Gene Symbol: TaASR3-A2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Pst21674 interaction with the abscisic acid-, stress-, and ripening-induced protein TaASR3 was validated mainly in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCPK5</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g229100.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g229100.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2D02G229100.1 Gene Symbol: TaCPK5 Gene Name: Ca2+-dependent protein kinase 5 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaTHI2 interacts with Ca2+-dependent protein kinase TaCPK5 to suppress virus infection by regulating ROS accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCRK10</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacrk10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacrk10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCRK10 Gene Name: Cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase 10 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The RLK protein TaCRK10 activates wheat high-temperature seedling-plant resistance to stripe rust through interacting with TaH2A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCRK2</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacrk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacrk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCRK2 Gene Name: cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: A novel cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase gene, TaCRK2, contributes to leaf rust resistance in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCSN5</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacsn5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacsn5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCSN5 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: A wheat COP9 subunit 5-like gene (TaCSN5) is negatively involved in host response to leaf rust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCT1-5A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCT1-5A Gene Name: copper transporter1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterization of a novel copper transporter gene family TaCT1 in common wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCT1-5B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCT1-5B Gene Name: copper transporter1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterization of a novel copper transporter gene family TaCT1 in common wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCT1-5D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tact1-5d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCT1-5D Gene Name: copper transporter1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterization of a novel copper transporter gene family TaCT1 in common wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGAPDH2-2A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g344600.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g344600.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2A02G344600.1 Gene Symbol: TaGAPDH2-2A Gene Name: glyceraldehyde-3-phosphate dehydrogenase 2 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGAPDH2-2B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g342200.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g342200.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2B02G342200.1 Gene Symbol: TaGAPDH2-2B Gene Name: glyceraldehyde-3-phosphate dehydrogenase 2 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGAPDH2-2D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g322900.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g322900.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCs2D02G322900.1 Gene Symbol: TaGAPDH2-2D Gene Name: glyceraldehyde-3-phosphate dehydrogenase 2 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaHOS15-A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaHOS15-A Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat WD40-repeat protein TaHOS15 functions in a histone deacetylase complex to fine-tune defense responses to Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaHOS15-B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaHOS15-B Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat WD40-repeat protein TaHOS15 functions in a histone deacetylase complex to fine-tune defense responses to Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaHOS15-D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tahos15-d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaHOS15-D Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat WD40-repeat protein TaHOS15 functions in a histone deacetylase complex to fine-tune defense responses to Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-A Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-B Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamed25-d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-D Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNADK2</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanadk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanadk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaNADK2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Subsequent investigations revealed that Pst03724 interferes with the TaCaM3-2B–NAD kinase (NADK) TaNADK2 association and thus inhibits the enzyme activity of TaNADK2 activated by TaCaM3-2B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNPSN11</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaNPSN11 Gene Name: soluble N-ethylmaleimide-sensitive factor attachment protein receptor 11 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Cloned and characterized three NPSN genes (TaNPSN11, TaNPSN12, and TaNPSN13) and three plant defence-related SNARE homologues (TaSYP132, TaSNAP34, and TaMEMB12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNPSN12</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaNPSN12 Gene Name: soluble N-ethylmaleimide-sensitive factor attachment protein receptor 12 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Cloned and characterized three NPSN genes (TaNPSN11, TaNPSN12, and TaNPSN13) and three plant defence-related SNARE homologues (TaSYP132, TaSNAP34, and TaMEMB12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNPSN13</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanpsn13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaNPSN13 Gene Name: soluble N-ethylmaleimide-sensitive factor attachment protein receptor 13 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Cloned and characterized three NPSN genes (TaNPSN11, TaNPSN12, and TaNPSN13) and three plant defence-related SNARE homologues (TaSYP132, TaSNAP34, and TaMEMB12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSYP132</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasyp132/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasyp132/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaSYP132 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Cloned and characterized three NPSN genes (TaNPSN11, TaNPSN12, and TaNPSN13) and three plant defence-related SNARE homologues (TaSYP132, TaSNAP34, and TaMEMB12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaTHI2-7A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7a02g376800.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7a02g376800.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS7A02G376800.1 Gene Symbol: TaTHI2-7A Gene Name: thiamine thiazole synthase Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaTHI2 interacts with Ca2+-dependent protein kinase TaCPK5 to suppress virus infection by regulating ROS accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaTHI2-7B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7b02g278200.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7b02g278200.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS7B02G278200.1 Gene Symbol: TaTHI2-7B Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaTHI2 interacts with Ca2+-dependent protein kinase TaCPK5 to suppress virus infection by regulating ROS accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaTHI2-7D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7d02g373100.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs7d02g373100.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS7D02G373100.2 Gene Symbol: TaTHI2-7D Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaTHI2 interacts with Ca2+-dependent protein kinase TaCPK5 to suppress virus infection by regulating ROS accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWIR1a</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaWIR1a Gene Name: Wheat-Induced Resistance 1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaWIR1 contributes to post-penetration resistance to Magnaporthe oryzae, but not Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWIR1b</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaWIR1b Gene Name: Wheat-Induced Resistance 1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaWIR1 contributes to post-penetration resistance to Magnaporthe oryzae, but not Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWIR1c</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawir1c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaWIR1c Gene Name: Wheat-Induced Resistance 1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaWIR1 contributes to post-penetration resistance to Magnaporthe oryzae, but not Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
