<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cold on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/cold/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cold on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/cold/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AaBAM3.1</title>
      <link>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aabam3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aabam3.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaBAM3.1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia arguta Functional Descriptions: The AaCBF4-AaBAM3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaCBF4</title>
      <link>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aacbf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aacbf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaCBF4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia arguta Functional Descriptions: The AaCBF4-AaBAM3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTIN7;act1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/actin7act1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/actin7act1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb348450 Gene Symbol: ACTIN7 act1 Gene Name: actin1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP59;OsBIERF3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g43790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g43790/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g43790 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0654700 Gene Symbol: AP59 OsBIERF3 OsAP59 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnCBF17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bncbf17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bncbf17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnCBF17 Gene Name: CBF-like protein CBF17 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Cold acclimation and BnCBF17-over-expression enhance photosynthetic performance and energy conversion efficiency during long-term growth of Brassica napus under elevated CO2 conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRZAT12</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_campestris/brzat12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_campestris/brzat12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Bra002528 Gene Symbol: BRZAT12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Description: BrZAT12 gene could improve the cold resistance of winter B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bZIP68;ABI5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/bzip68abi5zmabf3zmbzip33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/bzip68abi5zmabf3zmbzip33/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb176680 Gene Symbol: bZIP68 ABI5 ZmABF3 ZmbZIP33 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 68 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaCIPK13</title>
      <link>/genes/capsicum_annuum/cacipk13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/capsicum_annuum/cacipk13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CA05g16710 Gene Symbol: CaCIPK13 Gene Name: Capsicum annuum CBL-interacting protein kinases Genome: Pepper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaM6</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/cam6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/cam6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g098050 Gene Symbol: CaM6 Gene Name: CALMODULIN6 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaMYB340</title>
      <link>/genes/capsicum_annuum/camyb340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/capsicum_annuum/camyb340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CaMYB340 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Description: Transient CaMYB340 silencing increased FA desaturation and lowered electrolyte leakage, enhancing cold tolerance in CaMYB340 knockdown fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDS1;OsCNGC9</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g38580/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g38580/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g38580 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0558300 Gene Symbol: CDS1 OsCNGC9 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmLOX08</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/melo3c011885/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/melo3c011885/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MELO3C011885 Gene Symbol: CmLOX08 Gene Name: Lipoxygenase 8 Genome: Species: Cucumis melo Functional Descriptions: Cloned the CmLOX08 promoter of melon (Cucumis melo) and identified the main promoter regions regulating transcription in response to signalling molecules and abiotic stresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmPRR3</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmprr3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmprr3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MELO3C012470.2.1 Gene Symbol: CmPRR3 Gene Name: Genome: Melon (DHL92) v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmRR6</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmrr6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmrr6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MELO3C019056.2.1 Gene Symbol: CmRR6 Gene Name: Genome: Melon (DHL92) v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrNCED1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-reshni/crnced1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-reshni/crnced1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CrNCED1 Gene Name: 9-cis-epoxycarotenoid dioxygenase1 Genome: Species: Citrus reshni Functional Descriptions: Molecular cloning and characterization of CrNCED1, a gene encoding 9-cis-epoxycarotenoid dioxygenase in Citrus reshni, with functions in tolerance to multiple abiotic stresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbHLH18</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g024930m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g024930m/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: orange1.1g024930m Gene Symbol: CsbHLH18 Gene Name: basic helix–loop–helix transcription factor 18 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor CsbHLH18 of sweet orange functions in modulation of cold tolerance and homeostasis of reactive oxygen species by regulating the antioxidant gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsBPC2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsBPC2 Gene Name: BASIC PENTACYSTEINE 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsBPC2 knockout reduced cucumber cold tolerance by increasing the chilling injury index, relative electrical conductivity and malondialdehyde (MDA) content and decreasing antioxidant enzyme activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs5g10240 Gene Symbol: CsCBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCOR413PM2</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscor413pm2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscor413pm2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa_2G238250.1 Gene Symbol: CsCOR413PM2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Suppression of CsCOR413PM2 decreased cold tolerance of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGPA1</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgpa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgpa1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa_4G648550.1 Gene Symbol: CsGPA1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Mechanism of CsGPA1 in regulating cold tolerance of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHSFA1d</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g008920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g008920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G008920 Gene Symbol: CsHSFA1d Gene Name: heat-shock transcription factor HSFA1d Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Report that heat shock induces cold acclimation in cucumber seedlings, via a process involving the heat-shock transcription factor HSFA1d.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsINV5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csinv5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csinv5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsINV5 Gene Name: Vacuolar invertase 5 Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsINV5, a tea vacuolar invertase gene enhances cold tolerance in transgenic Arabidopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYBL2a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmybl2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmybl2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMYBL2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsMYBL2 homologs modulate the light and temperature stress-regulated anthocyanin and catechins biosynthesis in tea plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYBL2b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmybl2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmybl2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMYBL2b Gene Name: Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsMYBL2 homologs modulate the light and temperature stress-regulated anthocyanin and catechins biosynthesis in tea plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRuby1</title>
      <link>/genes/citrus_sinensis/csruby1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrus_sinensis/csruby1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsRuby1 Gene Name: Citrus sinensis Ruby1 Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYC-B</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/cyc-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/cyc-b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc06g074240 Gene Symbol: CYC-B Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgATX</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgatx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgatx/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: DgATX Gene Name: Chrysanthemum morifolium ARABIDOPSIS HOMOLOG OF TRITHORAX Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgbZIP3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgbzip3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgbzip3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DgbZIP3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: DgbZIP3 interacts with DgbZIP2 to increase the expression of DgPOD for cold stress tolerance in chrysanthemum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgMYB</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgmyb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgmyb/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: DgMYB Gene Name: Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgMYB2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgmyb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgmyb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DgMYB2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 2 Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: DgMYB2 improves cold resistance in chrysanthemum by directly targeting DgGPX1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgnsLTP</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgnsltp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgnsltp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DgnsLTP Gene Name: nonspecific lipid transfer protein Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Ubiquitin membrane yeast two-hybrid (MYTH) system and bimolecular fluorescence complementation (BIFC) assays showed that DgTIL1 interacts with a nonspecific lipid transfer protein (DgnsLTP), which can promote peroxidase (POD) gene expression and POD activity to reduce the accumulation of reactive oxygen species (ROS) and improve resistance to cold stress in DgnsLTP transgenic chrysanthemum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgTIL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgtil1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/dgtil1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DgTIL1 Gene Name: temperature-induced lipocalin-1-like Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Identified a temperature-induced lipocalin-1-like gene (DgTIL1) from chrysanthemum and showed that it was notably induced in response to cold stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DgTIL1</title>
      <link>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgtil1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/dgtil1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: DgTIL1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Lysine crotonylation of DgTIL1 at K72 modulates cold tolerance by enhancing DgnsLTP stability in chrysanthemum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkNAC9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dknac9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dknac9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkNAC9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: High CO2/hypoxia-induced softening of persimmon fruit is modulated by DkERF8/16 and DkNAC9 complexes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EFA27;OsClo5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g43200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g43200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g43200 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0511200 Gene Symbol: EFA27 OsClo5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EguCBF1a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/eucalyptus-gunnii/egucbf1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/eucalyptus-gunnii/egucbf1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: EguCBF1a Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor 1 Genome: Species: Eucalyptus gunnii Functional Descriptions: Two C-repeat binding factor genes (EguCBF1a/EguCBF1b), isolated from E.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EguCBF1b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/eucalyptus-gunnii/egucbf1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/eucalyptus-gunnii/egucbf1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: EguCBF1b Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor 1 Genome: Species: Eucalyptus gunnii Functional Descriptions: Two C-repeat binding factor genes (EguCBF1a/EguCBF1b), isolated from E.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FcWRKY70</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fortunella-crassifolia/fcwrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fortunella-crassifolia/fcwrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FcWRKY70 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 70 Genome: Species: Fortunella crassifolia Functional Descriptions: FcWRKY70, a WRKY protein of Fortunella crassifolia, functions in drought tolerance and modulates putrescine synthesis by regulating arginine decarboxylase gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhDREB1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghdreb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghdreb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhDREB1 Gene Name: DREB-like transcription factor Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton GhDREB1 increases plant tolerance to low temperature and is negatively regulated by gibberellic acid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhHSP70-26</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghhsp70-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghhsp70-26/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gohir.D06G173000 Gene Symbol: GhHSP70-26 Gene Name: Genome: Gossypium hirsutum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmDREB3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmdreb3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmdreb3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmDREB3 Gene Name: dehydration-responsive element binding protein 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Cold-induced modulation and functional analyses of the DRE-binding transcription factor gene, GmDREB3, in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmERF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmerf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmerf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmERF3 Gene Name: EREBP/AP2 transcription factor Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of the soybean GmERF3 gene, an AP2/ERF type transcription factor for increased tolerances to salt, drought, and diseases in transgenic tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFAD7-1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmfad7-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmfad7-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmFAD7-1 Gene Name: omega-3 fatty acid desaturase Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Genomic sequencing analysis together with searches at the soybean genome database further confirmed that both GmFAD7 genes were located in two different loci within the soybean genome, suggesting that the soybean ω3 plastidial desaturase FAD7 is encoded by two different paralogous genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFAD7-2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmfad7-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmfad7-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmFAD7-2 Gene Name: omega-3 fatty acid desaturase Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Genomic sequencing analysis together with searches at the soybean genome database further confirmed that both GmFAD7 genes were located in two different loci within the soybean genome, suggesting that the soybean ω3 plastidial desaturase FAD7 is encoded by two different paralogous genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSIZ1a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.12g071300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.12g071300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.12g071300 Gene Symbol: GmSIZ1a Gene Name: SUMO E3 ligase 1 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: SUMO E3 Ligases GmSIZ1a and GmSIZ1b regulate vegetative growth in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSIZ1b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.u020100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.u020100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.U020100 Gene Symbol: GmSIZ1b Gene Name: SUMO E3 ligase 1 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: SUMO E3 Ligases GmSIZ1a and GmSIZ1b regulate vegetative growth in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvOS2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvos2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvos2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvOS2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Fine-tuning of the flowering time control in winter barley: the importance of HvOS2 and HvVRN2 in non-inductive conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbSnRK1</title>
      <link>/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbSnRK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: These results show that the IbSnRK1 gene confers salt, drought, and cold tolerance in sweet potato by activating the ROS scavenging system and controlling stomatal closure via the ABA signaling pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/ice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/ice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g118310 Gene Symbol: ICE1 Gene Name: INDUCER of CBF EXPRESSION 1 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAS;TSV2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g33500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g33500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g33500 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0538000 Gene Symbol: LAS TSV2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTG5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g45110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g45110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g45110 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0527100 Gene Symbol: LTG5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTT1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g34110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g34110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g34110 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0482200 Gene Symbol: LTT1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaBEL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma01_g01710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma01_g01710/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma01_g01710 Gene Symbol: MaBEL1 Gene Name: BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaBEL1 regulates banana fruit ripening by activating cell wall and starch degradation-related genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaC2H2-IDD</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mac2h2-idd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mac2h2-idd/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaC2H2-IDD Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaC2H2-IDD regulates fruit softening and involved in softening disorder induced by cold stress in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaICE1 Gene Name: transcription factor ICE1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Banana fruit NAC transcription factor MaNAC1 is a direct target of MaICE1 and involved in cold stress through interacting with MaCBF1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g34790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g34790/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma06_g34790 Gene Symbol: MaMAPK3|MaMAPK3a Gene Name: Genome: genome database of Musa (http://banana-genome-hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdbHLH33</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbhlh33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbhlh33/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MdbHLH33 Gene Name: Malus domestica basic helix-loop-helix 33 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBIM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000143208/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000143208 Gene Symbol: MdBIM1 Gene Name: BES1-INTERACTING MYC-LIKE PROTEIN1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Brassinosteroid signaling regulator BIM1 (MdBIM1) integrates brassinolide and jasmonic acid signaling during cold tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdCIbHLH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdcibhlh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdcibhlh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdCIbHLH1 Gene Name: Cold-Induced bHLH1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The cold-induced basic helix-loop-helix transcription factor gene MdCIbHLH1encodes an ICE-like protein in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdHDA6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdhda6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdhda6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdHDA6 Gene Name: HISTONE DEACETYLASE 6 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: histone deacetylase 6 (MdHDA6), which negatively regulates apple drought tolerance by catalyzing deacetylation on histones associated with drought-responsive genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdHYL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdhyl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdhyl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdHYL1 Gene Name: HYPONASTIC LEAVES1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The RNA-binding protein MdHYL1 modulates cold tolerance and disease resistance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000662999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000662999/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000662999 Gene Symbol: MdICE1 Gene Name: MYC-type bHLH transcription factor ICE1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Further study showed that MdPUB23 directly interacted with MdICE1, promoting the ubiquitination-mediated degradation of the MdICE1 protein through the 26S-proteasome pathway and reducing the MdICE1-improved cold-stress tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdJAZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000452772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000452772/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000452772 Gene Symbol: MdJAZ1 Gene Name: jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) protein 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) proteins MdJAZ1 and MdJAZ2 negatively modulate MdABI4-improved cold tolerance in apple by interacting with the MdABI4 protein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdJAZ2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/mdp0000757701/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/mdp0000757701/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000757701 Gene Symbol: MdJAZ2 Gene Name: jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) protein 2 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: The jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) proteins MdJAZ1 and MdJAZ2 negatively modulate MdABI4-improved cold tolerance in apple by interacting with the MdABI4 protein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMIEL1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmiel1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmiel1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MdMIEL1 Gene Name: MYB30-INTERACTING E3 LIGASE 1 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMRLK2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmrlk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmrlk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD12G1190700 Gene Symbol: MdMRLK2 Gene Name: Malus domestica FERONIA receptor-like kinase 2 Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB23</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000230141/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000230141/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000230141 Gene Symbol: MdMYB23 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 23 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: R2R3-MYB transcription factor MdMYB23 is involved in the cold tolerance and proanthocyanidin accumulation in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB308L</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb308l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdmyb308l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000950559 Gene Symbol: MdMYB308L Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdNAC104</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdnac104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdnac104/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD15G1415700 Gene Symbol: MdNAC104 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdPUB23</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md14g1040300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md14g1040300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD14G1040300 Gene Symbol: MdPUB23 Gene Name: U-box-type E3 ubiquitin ligase Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Apple U-box-type E3 ubiquitin ligase MdPUB23 reduces cold-stress tolerance by degrading the cold-stress regulatory protein MdICE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdTCP15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md13g1073500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md13g1073500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD13G1073500 Gene Symbol: MdTCP15 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Histone deacetylase MdHDA6 is an antagonist in regulation of transcription factor MdTCP15 to promote cold tolerance in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdWRKY40is</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky40is/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdwrky40is/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD15G1039500 Gene Symbol: MdWRKY40is Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MfAOC2</title>
      <link>/genes/medicago_sativa/mfaoc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/medicago_sativa/mfaoc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MfAOC2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results suggest that expression of MfAOC2 or MtAOC2 promotes biosynthesis of JA, which positively regulates expression of CBF genes and antioxidant defense under cold conditions and expression of JA downstream genes after pathogen infection, leading to greater cold tolerance and pathogen resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MhDREB2A</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mhdreb2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mhdreb2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MhDREB2A Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MhZAT10</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mhzat10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mhzat10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD08G1086500 Gene Symbol: MhZAT10 Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCML42</title>
      <link>/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtcml42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtcml42/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MtCML42 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNAC80</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtnac80/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtnac80/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g094580 Gene Symbol: MtNAC80 Gene Name: NAC domain-containing protein 80 Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusaDHN-1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musadhn-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musadhn-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MusaDHN-1 Gene Name: SK3-type dehydrin Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MusaDHN-1, a novel multiple stress-inducible SK3-type dehydrin gene, contributes affirmatively to drought- and salt-stress tolerance in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusaPIP1;2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musapip12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musapip12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MusaPIP1;2 Gene Name: Aquaporin PIP1-2 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Transgenic banana plants overexpressing a native plasma membrane aquaporin MusaPIP1;2 display high tolerance levels to different abiotic stresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOG1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g54860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g54860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g54860 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0752200 Gene Symbol: NOG1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osa-miR1320</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/osa-mir1320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/osa-mir1320/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: None RAPdb gene ID: None Gene Symbol: Osa-miR1320 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsBIRH1;TCD33</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g01830/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g01830/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g01830 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0108600 Gene Symbol: OsBIRH1 TCD33 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsBRXL5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g27230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g27230/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g27230 ,LOC_Os09g27220 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0444500 ,Os09g0444600 Gene Symbol: OsBRXL5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsBSK2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g42110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g42110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g42110 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0571300 Gene Symbol: OsBSK2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCAF1B</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g58810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g58810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g58810 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0684900 Gene Symbol: OsCAF1B Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCRP1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g39180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g39180/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g39180 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0565200 Gene Symbol: OsCRP1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCRT3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g67054/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g67054/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g67054 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0895600 Gene Symbol: OsCRT3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsDLK</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g01490/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g01490/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g01490 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0105700 Gene Symbol: OsDLK Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsDof1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09720/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09720/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g09720 RAPdb gene ID: NONE Gene Symbol: OsDof1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsERF096</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g41330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g41330/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g41330 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0562900 Gene Symbol: OsERF096 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGATA16</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g37450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g37450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g37450 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0571800 Gene Symbol: OsGATA16 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGATL5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g44850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g44850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g44850 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0530900 Gene Symbol: OsGATL5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGF14d</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g34450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g34450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g34450 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0546900 Gene Symbol: OsGF14d Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGRF6</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g51970/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g51970/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g51970 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0729500 Gene Symbol: OsGRF6 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsLEA9</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g21250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g21250/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g21250 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0314800 Gene Symbol: OsLEA9 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsLPXC</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g12320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g12320/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g12320 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0223900 Gene Symbol: OsLPXC Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsLUX;OsPCL1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g74020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g74020/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g74020 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0971800 Gene Symbol: OsLUX OsPCL1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMKKK70</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g50410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g50410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g50410 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0699500 Gene Symbol: OsMKKK70 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMYB30;OsMYB5P</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g41510/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g41510/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g41510 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0624300 Gene Symbol: OsMYB30 OsMYB5P Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMYB38</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42870/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g42870 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0641900 Gene Symbol: OsMYB38 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsOAT</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g44150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g44150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g44150 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0643300 Gene Symbol: OsOAT Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPP2C27</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g55560/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g55560/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g55560 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0799000 Gene Symbol: OsPP2C27 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPPR676;OsATP4</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g11670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g11670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g11670 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0215900 Gene Symbol: OsPPR676 OsATP4 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRab11C1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g47730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g47730/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g47730 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0667600 Gene Symbol: OsRab11C1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRING-1;OsATL38</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g52210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g52210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g52210 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0759400 Gene Symbol: OsRING-1 OsATL38 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRR6</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g57720/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g57720/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g57720 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0673300 Gene Symbol: OsRR6 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSEH1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g43250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g43250/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g43250 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0620100 Gene Symbol: OsSEH1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSRDP</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g59420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g59420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g59420 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0690500 Gene Symbol: OsSRDP Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTMF</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g48620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g48620/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g48620 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0559900 Gene Symbol: OsTMF Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTZF5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g03760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g03760/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g03760 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0128200 Gene Symbol: OsTZF5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsUGT90A1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g24110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g24110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g24110 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0305700 Gene Symbol: OsUGT90A1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWRKY115</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g27670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g27670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g27670 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0460900 Gene Symbol: OsWRKY115 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWRKY63</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g45920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g45920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g45920 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0686250 Gene Symbol: OsWRKY63 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaCBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-aphrodite/pacbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-aphrodite/pacbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PaCBF1 Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor1 Genome: Species: Phalaenopsis aphrodite Functional Descriptions: Cold Response in Phalaenopsis aphrodite and Characterization of PaCBF1 and PaICE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-aphrodite/paice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/phalaenopsis-aphrodite/paice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PaICE1 Gene Name: CBF expression1 Genome: Species: Phalaenopsis aphrodite Functional Descriptions: Cold Response in Phalaenopsis aphrodite and Characterization of PaCBF1 and PaICE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrWRKY53</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulaefolia/pbr018725.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-betulaefolia/pbr018725.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pbr018725.1 Gene Symbol: PbrWRKY53 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 53 Genome: Species: Pyrus betulaefolia Functional Descriptions: A WRKY transcription factor PbrWRKY53 from Pyrus betulaefolia is involved in drought tolerance and AsA accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeSTZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-euphratica/pestz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-euphratica/pestz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PeSTZ1 Gene Name: SALT TOLERANCE ZINC FINGER 1 Genome: Species: Populus euphratica Functional Descriptions: PeSTZ1, a C2H2-type zinc finger transcription factor from Populus euphratica, enhances freezing tolerance through modulation of ROS scavenging by directly regulating PeAPX2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpCBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppcbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppcbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PpCBF1 Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor 1 Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: The overexpression of a peach CBF (PpCBF1) gene in a transgenic line of own-rooted apple (Malus×domestica) M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpDML1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.7g118000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.7g118000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.7G118000 Gene Symbol: PpDML1 Gene Name: DNA demethylase1 Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor PpNAC1 and DNA demethylase PpDML1 synergistically regulate peach fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpINH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.5g112600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.5g112600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.5G112600 Gene Symbol: PpINH1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: PpINH1, an invertase inhibitor, interacts with vacuolar invertase PpVIN2 in regulating the chilling tolerance of peach fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsbHLH3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/evm.tu.chr8.2504/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/evm.tu.chr8.2504/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: evm.TU.Chr8.2504 Gene Symbol: PsbHLH3 Gene Name: Genome: ‘Sanyueli’ plum (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsERF1B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/evm.tu.chr8.2346/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/evm.tu.chr8.2346/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: evm.TU.Chr8.2346 Gene Symbol: PsERF1B Gene Name: Genome: ‘Sanyueli’ plum (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsMYB10.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/novel_g001502/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-salicina/novel_g001502/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: novel_G001502 Gene Symbol: PsMYB10.1 Gene Name: Genome: ‘Sanyueli’ plum (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtaZFP2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/ptazfp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/ptazfp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PtaZFP2 Gene Name: Cys2/His2 zinc finger protein Genome: Species: Populus tremula x Populus alba Functional Descriptions: A single bending modified plant diameter growth and increased the relative abundance of PtaZFP2 transcripts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrA;NINV7</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptraninv7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptraninv7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt9g000720 Gene Symbol: PtrA;NINV7 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrACS1</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptracs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptracs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt3g03800 Gene Symbol: PtrACS1 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrAHL14</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrahl14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrahl14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;PtUn005950 Gene Symbol: PtrAHL14 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrAHL17</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrahl17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrahl17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt5g010530 Gene Symbol: PtrAHL17 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrBADH-l</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrbadh-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrbadh-l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: PtrBADH-l Gene Name: Poncirus trifoliata BADH-like Genome: Species: Poncirus trifoliata Functional Description: we propose a transcriptional regulatory module PtrMYC2-PtrBADH-l to advance the understanding of molecular mechanisms underlying the GB accumulation under cold stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrbHLH</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-trifoliata/ptrbhlh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-trifoliata/ptrbhlh/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PtrbHLH Gene Name: Basic Helix-Loop-Helix Transcription Factor Genome: Species: Citrus trifoliata Functional Descriptions: A Basic Helix-Loop-Helix Transcription Factor, PtrbHLH, of Poncirus trifoliata Confers Cold Tolerance and Modulates Peroxidase-Mediated Scavenging of Hydrogen Peroxide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrERF108</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrerf108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrerf108/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt7g003200 Gene Symbol: PtrERF108 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrERF9</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrerf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrerf9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt2g011090 Gene Symbol: PtrERF9 Gene Name: Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrGSTU17</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrgstu17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrgstu17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pt4g003440 Gene Symbol: PtrGSTU17 Gene Name: glutathione S-transferase U17 Genome: P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrMYC2</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrmyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrmyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: PtrMYC2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Poncirus trifoliata Functional Description: we propose a transcriptional regulatory module PtrMYC2-PtrBADH-l to advance the understanding of molecular mechanisms underlying the GB accumulation under cold stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrRafS</title>
      <link>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrrafs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/poncirus_trifoliata/ptrrafs/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs9g12460 Gene Symbol: PtrRafS Gene Name: Genome: Species: Poncirus trifoliata Functional Description: The current results demonstrate that PtrERF108 plays a positive role in cold tolerance by modulation of raffinose synthesis via regulating PtrRafS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuMYB21</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuMYB21 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 21 Genome: Species: Pyrus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: PuMYB21 and PuMYB54, from “Nanguo” pears, which were notably expressed in response to cold stress and during the peel-browning process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuMYB54</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb54/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb54/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuMYB54 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 21 Genome: Species: Pyrus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: PuMYB21 and PuMYB54, from “Nanguo” pears, which were notably expressed in response to cold stress and during the peel-browning process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>qCTB7</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g07690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g07690/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g07690 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0173300 ,Os07g0173400 Gene Symbol: qCTB7 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScAREB4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.11g016910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.11g016910/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.11G016910 Gene Symbol: ScAREB4 Gene Name: ABA-responsive element binding protein 4 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: ScAREB4 promotes potato constitutive and acclimated freezing tolerance associated with enhancing trehalose synthesis and oxidative stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShPP2-1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/shpp2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/shpp2-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc05g055870 Gene Symbol: ShPP2-1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sicbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sicbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g124110 Gene Symbol: SICBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIWRKY33</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/siwrky33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/siwrky33/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc09g014990 Gene Symbol: SIWRKY33 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlACO1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaco1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaco1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g049530 Gene Symbol: SlACO1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlACO4</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaco4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaco4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g081190 Gene Symbol: SlACO4 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlACR11A</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slacr11a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slacr11a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g117890 Gene Symbol: SlACR11A Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAOS</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slaos/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc04g079730 Gene Symbol: SlAOS Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlBBX17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g052620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g052620/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc07g052620 Gene Symbol: SlBBX17 Gene Name: BBX transcription factor 17 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlMPK1- and SlMPK2-mediated SlBBX17 phosphorylation positively regulates CBF-dependent cold tolerance in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlBCH1b</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbch1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbch1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc06g036260 Gene Symbol: SlBCH1b Gene Name: β-RING CAROTENE HYDROXYLASE 1b Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlBRI1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slbri1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slbri1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlBRI1 Gene Name: BRASSINOSTEROID INSENSITIVE 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of SlBRI1 driven by the Atrd29A promoter could increase the cold resistance of tomato plants during chilling stress but did not improve the expression of SlBRI1 and plant growth under normal conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlCBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g026280 Gene Symbol: SlCBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlCBF2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g124110 Gene Symbol: SlCBF2 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlCBF3</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slcbf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc03g026270 Gene Symbol: SlCBF3 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlFHY3</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slfhy3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slfhy3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g043270 Gene Symbol: SlFHY3 Gene Name: FAR-RED ELONGATED HYPOCOTYL3 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlGRAS4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc01g100200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc01g100200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc01g100200 Gene Symbol: SlGRAS4 Gene Name: GRAS transcription factor 4 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlGRAS4 mediates a novel regulatory pathway promoting chilling tolerance in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlHY5</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slhy5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slhy5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g061130 Gene Symbol: SlHY5 Gene Name: ELONGATED HYPOCOTYL5 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMPK2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g014420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g014420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc08g014420 Gene Symbol: SlMPK2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlMPK1- and SlMPK2-mediated SlBBX17 phosphorylation positively regulates CBF-dependent cold tolerance in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMYB15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solyc03g005570/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solyc03g005570/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc03g005570 Gene Symbol: SlMYB15 Gene Name: SlMYB15 transcription factor Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato SlMYB15 transcription factor targeted by sly-miR156e-3p positively regulates ABA-mediated cold tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlNAC3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g063420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g063420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc07G063420 Gene Symbol: SlNAC3 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 3 Genome: Solanum_lycopersicum SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlNAM3</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slnam3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slnam3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc06g069710 Gene Symbol: SlNAM3 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPIF4</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slpif4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slpif4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g043580 Gene Symbol: SlPIF4 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlREC2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slrec2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slrec2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc07g006030 Gene Symbol: SlREC2 Gene Name: 9-CIS-EPOXYCAROTENOID DIOXYGENASE 2 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlWRKY50</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwrky50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwrky50/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc06g068460 Gene Symbol: SlWRKY50 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StABF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StABF1 Gene Name: ABRE binding factor1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StABF1, a stress-responsive bZIP transcription factor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StAmy23</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400009891/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400009891/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400009891 Gene Symbol: StAmy23 Gene Name: alpha-amylase 23 Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBAM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400001549/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400001549/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400001549 Gene Symbol: StBAM1 Gene Name: Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBAM9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400010664/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400010664/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400010664 Gene Symbol: StBAM9 Gene Name: Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StInvInh2A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StInvInh2A Gene Name: Shepody putative invertase inhibitor Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StInvInh2 as an inhibitor of StvacINV1 regulates the cold-induced sweetening of potato tubers by specifically capping vacuolar invertase activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StInvInh2B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StInvInh2B Gene Name: ND860-2 putative invertase inhibitor Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StInvInh2 as an inhibitor of StvacINV1 regulates the cold-induced sweetening of potato tubers by specifically capping vacuolar invertase activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPPI1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stppi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stppi1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPPI1 Gene Name: proton pump interactor 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StPPI1, a proton pump interactor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTINY3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G035540.1 Gene Symbol: StTINY3 Gene Name: CBF/DREB transcription factor3 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor StTINY3 enhances cold-induced sweetening resistance by coordinating starch resynthesis and sucrose hydrolysis in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCBF14</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacbf14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacbf14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCBF14 Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor 14 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic barley lines prove the involvement of TaCBF14 and TaCBF15 in the cold acclimation process and in frost tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCBF15</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacbf15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacbf15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCBF15 Gene Name: C-repeat binding factor 15 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic barley lines prove the involvement of TaCBF14 and TaCBF15 in the cold acclimation process and in frost tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCOLD1-2A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g438900.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g438900.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2A02G438900.1 Gene Symbol: TaCOLD1-2A Gene Name: GPCR-type G protein COLD1-like Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaCOLD1 defines a new regulator of plant height in bread wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCOLD1-2B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g458500.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g458500.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2B02G458500.1 Gene Symbol: TaCOLD1-2B Gene Name: GPCR-type G protein COLD1-like Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaCOLD1 defines a new regulator of plant height in bread wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCOLD1-2D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g435300.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g435300.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2D02G435300.1 Gene Symbol: TaCOLD1-2D Gene Name: GPCR-type G protein COLD1-like Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaCOLD1 defines a new regulator of plant height in bread wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGRP2</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagrp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tagrp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4B02G020300 Gene Symbol: TaGRP2 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaICE41</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taice41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taice41/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaICE41 Gene Name: ICE1-like 41 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Two different inducers of CBF expression (ICE1-like genes), TaICE41 and TaICE87, were isolated from a cDNA library prepared from cold-treated wheat aerial tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaICE87</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taice87/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taice87/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaICE87 Gene Name: ICE1-like 87 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Two different inducers of CBF expression (ICE1-like genes), TaICE41 and TaICE87, were isolated from a cDNA library prepared from cold-treated wheat aerial tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaPAP6L−2B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tapap6l2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tapap6l2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS2B02G171300 Gene Symbol: TaPAP6L−2B Gene Name: plastid‐lipid‐associated protein 6, chloroplastic‐like Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaPGK</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tapgk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tapgk/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS6B02G187500 Gene Symbol: TaPGK Gene Name: Phosphoglycerate Kinase (PGK) Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaRAP2.1L</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tarap2.1l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tarap2.1l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaRAP2.1L Gene Name: RAC875 drought responsive element binding transcription factor Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The wheat DREB/CBF gene TaRAP2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSnRK1α−1A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasnrk1%CE%B11a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasnrk1%CE%B11a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS1A02G350500 Gene Symbol: TaSnRK1α−1A Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRT1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS2B02G092700 Gene Symbol: TaSRT1 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaVRN1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tavrn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tavrn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5A02G391700 Gene Symbol: TaVRN1 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWRKY70</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaWRKY70 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 70 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: There is no direct evidence as to whether WRKY transcription factors play a role in HTSP resistance to Pst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGT91Q2</title>
      <link>/genes/camellia_sinensis/ugt91q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/camellia_sinensis/ugt91q2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: UGT91Q2 Gene Name: Genome: TeaPGDB V1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VaPAT1</title>
      <link>/genes/vitis_amurensis/vapat1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/vitis_amurensis/vapat1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: VaPAT1 Gene Name: Genome: itis vinifera Genome (12×) Species: Vitis amurensis Functional Description: these findings point to a pivotal role of VaPAT1 in the cold stress response in grape by regulating JA biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VpPUB24</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-pseudoreticulata/vppub24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-pseudoreticulata/vppub24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VpPUB24 Gene Name: putative U-box protein 24 Genome: Species: Vitis pseudoreticulata Functional Descriptions: VpPUB24, a novel gene from Chinese grapevine, Vitis pseudoreticulata, targets VpICE1 to enhance cold tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvBAM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvbam1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvbam1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvBAM1 Gene Name: beta-amylase 1 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: Genome-wide identification of BAM genes in grapevine (Vitis vinifera L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvCBF4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/vvcbf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/vvcbf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvCBF4 Gene Name: C-repeat binding protein 4 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: To overcome such production losses, a recently identified grapevine C-repeat binding factor (CBF) gene, VvCBF4, was overexpressed in grape vine cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmABCC;mrpa6</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmabccmrpa6zmabcb21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmabccmrpa6zmabcb21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb341220 Gene Symbol: ZmABCC mrpa6 ZmABCB21 Gene Name: multidrug resistance associated protein6 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmC2H2-81;cchh133</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmc2h2-81cchh133/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmc2h2-81cchh133/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb243510 Gene Symbol: ZmC2H2-81 cchh133 Gene Name: Cys2His2 Zinc Finger133 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCOI6.1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmcoi6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmcoi6.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb398970 Gene Symbol: ZmCOI6.1 Gene Name: stress inducible protein coi6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCPK1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb002180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb002180/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb002180 Gene Symbol: ZmCPK1|ZmCPK7|ZmCDPK3|cdpk36 Gene Name: calcium dependent protein kinase36 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmEREB92;ereb92</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmereb92ereb92/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmereb92ereb92/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb352580 Gene Symbol: ZmEREB92 ereb92 Gene Name: AP2-EREBP-transcription factor 92 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmG6PDH1;gpdh1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmg6pdh1gpdh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmg6pdh1gpdh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb079220 Gene Symbol: ZmG6PDH1 gpdh1 Gene Name: glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmG6PDH4;G6PD2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmg6pdh4g6pd2gpdh4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmg6pdh4g6pd2gpdh4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb019890 Gene Symbol: ZmG6PDH4 G6PD2 gpdh4 Gene Name: glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGPAT10;ZmGPA10</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmgpat10zmgpa10gpat8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmgpat10zmgpa10gpat8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb159140 Gene Symbol: ZmGPAT10 ZmGPA10 gpat8 Gene Name: glycerol-3-phosphate acyltransferase8 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGPAT8;ZmGPAT6</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmgpat8zmgpat6gpat6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmgpat8zmgpat6gpat6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb136910 Gene Symbol: ZmGPAT8 ZmGPAT6 gpat6 Gene Name: glycerol-3-phosphate acyltransferase6 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGRXCC5;grx12</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmgrxcc5grx12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmgrxcc5grx12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb121020 Gene Symbol: ZmGRXCC5 grx12 Gene Name: glutaredoxin12 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmHSP2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmhsp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmhsp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb002790 Gene Symbol: ZmHSP2 Gene Name: Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmHSP2;ZmGST2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmhsp2zmgst2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmhsp2zmgst2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb002790 Gene Symbol: ZmHSP2 ZmGST2 Gene Name: glutathione S-transferase12 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GRMZM25173534 Gene Symbol: ZmICE1 Gene Name: Genome: B73_RefGen_v3 Species: Zea mays Functional Descriptions: As AtYODA acts as a molecular switch in stomatal differentiation and O11 interacts with ZmICE1 and directly regulates ZmYoda, we speculated that ZmICE1 might also be involved in regulating ZmYoda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmICE1;ICE1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1ice1zmiceazmscrambhlh175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmice1ice1zmiceazmscrambhlh175/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb142500 Gene Symbol: ZmICE1 ICE1 ZmICEa ZmSCRAM bhlh175 Gene Name: INDUCER OF CBF EXPRESSION 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmLAZ1-5;laz5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmlaz1-5laz5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmlaz1-5laz5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb304160 Gene Symbol: ZmLAZ1-5 laz5 Gene Name: lazarus ortholog5 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMKK4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb257340 Gene Symbol: ZmMKK4 Gene Name: MAP kinase kinase4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMPK17</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb209160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb209160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb209160 Gene Symbol: ZmMPK17 Gene Name: MAP kinase17 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmPDIL2-2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmpdil2-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmpdil2-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb367110 Gene Symbol: ZmPDIL2-2 Gene Name: protein disulfide isomerase7 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmPEAMT;peamt1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmpeamtpeamt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmpeamtpeamt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb155940 Gene Symbol: ZmPEAMT peamt1 Gene Name: phosphoethanolamine N-methyltransferase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRAFS;ZmRS</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrafszmrsrafs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrafszmrsrafs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb122980 Gene Symbol: ZmRAFS ZmRS rafs1 Gene Name: raffinose synthase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRBOH5;rboh5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrboh5rboh5zmrbohh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrboh5rboh5zmrbohh/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb341910 Gene Symbol: ZmRBOH5 rboh5 ZmRbohH Gene Name: respiratory burst oxidase5 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRBOH8</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrboh8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrboh8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb040550 Gene Symbol: ZmRBOH8 Gene Name: respiratory burst oxidase8 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSnRK2.1;ZmSnRK2.3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsnrk2.1zmsnrk2.3snrkii3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsnrk2.1zmsnrk2.3snrkii3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb023880 Gene Symbol: ZmSnRK2.1 ZmSnRK2.3 snrkII3 Gene Name: SnRK2 serine threonine protein kinase3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
