<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bacterial disease on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/bacterial-disease/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bacterial disease on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/bacterial-disease/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AP59;OsBIERF3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g43790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g43790/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g43790 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0654700 Gene Symbol: AP59 OsBIERF3 OsAP59 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asr6;OsASR6</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g73250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g73250/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g73250 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0963600 Gene Symbol: Asr6 OsASR6 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLOB1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g27640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g27640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs7g27640 Gene Symbol: CsLOB1 Gene Name: Citrus sinensis lateral organ boundary 1 Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMKK5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhMKK5 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase kinase5 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton GhMKK5 affects disease resistance, induces HR-like cell death, and reduces the tolerance to salt and drought stress in transgenic Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeHB16</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/mehb16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/mehb16/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MeHB16 Gene Name: homeodomain leucine-zipper I (HD-Zip I) TF Genome: Species: Manihot esculenta Functional Descriptions: KIN10-mediated HB16 protein phosphorylation and self-association improve cassava disease resistance by transcriptional activation of lignin biosynthesis genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeKIN10</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/mekin10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/mekin10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MeKIN10 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Manihot esculenta Functional Descriptions: KIN10-mediated HB16 protein phosphorylation and self-association improve cassava disease resistance by transcriptional activation of lignin biosynthesis genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeNF-YC15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/menf-yc15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/manihot-esculenta/menf-yc15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MeNF-YC15 Gene Name: nuclear factor Y Genome: Species: Manihot esculenta Functional Descriptions: NF-YC15 transcription factor activates ethylene biosynthesis and improves cassava disease resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsDR11</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os12g27520/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os12g27520/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os12g27520 RAPdb gene ID: Os12g0460800 Gene Symbol: OsDR11 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCPK2-A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacpk2-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tacpk2-a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaCPK2-A Gene Name: calcium-dependent protein kinase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaCPK2-A, a calcium-dependent protein kinase gene that is required for wheat powdery mildew resistance enhances bacterial blight resistance in transgenic rice.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
