<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>root growth on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/root-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in root growth on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/root-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ACS7</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/acs7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/acs7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C03G066100 Gene Symbol: ACS7 Gene Name: carboxylate synthase 7 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: An allelic variant in the ACS7 gene promotes primary root growth in watermelon。 The ACS7 expression and ethylene levels in the primary root tips suggested that ethylene is a negative regulator of root elongation in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArPK</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g47780/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g47780/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g47780 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0693000 Gene Symbol: ArPK Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGE1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/bige1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/bige1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb211050 Gene Symbol: BIGE1 Gene Name: Big embryo 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnaA2.NIP5;1</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaa2.nip51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaa2.nip51/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;BraA02G0242800 Gene Symbol: BnaA2.NIP5 1 Gene Name: Genome: Darmor-bzh reference genome Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Specific and multiple-target gene silencing reveals function diversity of BnaA2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnaA3.NIP5;1</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaa3.nip51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaa3.nip51/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;BnaA03C0265800 Gene Symbol: BnaA3.NIP5;1 Gene Name: Genome: Darmor-bzh reference genome Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Specific and multiple-target gene silencing reveals function diversity of BnaA2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnaA4.BOR2</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaann31830d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/bnaann31830d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BnaAnn31830D Gene Symbol: BnaA4.BOR2 Gene Name: B efflux transporter Genome: Brassica napus Genome Resources Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: BnaA4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnaC4.BOR2</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/bnac04g21390d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/bnac04g21390d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BnaC04g21390D Gene Symbol: BnaC4.BOR2 Gene Name: low-B (LB)-inducible Genome: rapeseed genome Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: BnaC4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g46007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g46007/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi3g46007 Gene Symbol: BUZZ Gene Name: Genome: reference Bd21 genome Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: BUZZ: an essential gene for postinitiation root hair growth and a mediator of root architecture in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaSRP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/casrp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/casrp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaSRP1 Gene Name: stress-related protein 1 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Constitutive expression of CaSRP1, a hot pepper small rubber particle protein homolog, resulted in fast growth and improved drought tolerance in transgenic Arabidopsis plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcARP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccarp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccarp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcARP1 Gene Name: actin depolymerizing factor-related phosphokinase 1 Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: Melatonin-mediated CcARP1 alters F-actin dynamics by phosphorylation of CcADF9 to balance root growth and salt tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmNRRa</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmnrra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmnrra/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmNRRa Gene Name: Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: CmNRRa, an orthologous gene of OsNRRa that regulates root growth in response to nutrient stress in rice, was identified from Chrysanthemum and its role in flowering time was studied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cr4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/cr4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/cr4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb406780 Gene Symbol: Cr4 Gene Name: crinkly4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsBPC2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsBPC2 Gene Name: BASIC PENTACYSTEINE 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsBPC2 knockout reduced cucumber cold tolerance by increasing the chilling injury index, relative electrical conductivity and malondialdehyde (MDA) content and decreasing antioxidant enzyme activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsUGT84J2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TEA000239 Gene Symbol: CsUGT84J2 Gene Name: Al-induced glycosyltransferase Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: Found that flavonol glycoside levels in tea roots increased following Al treatment, and the Al-induced UDP glycosyltransferase CsUGT84J2 was involved in this mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D5;ZmTPS7</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/d5zmtps7zmtps44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/d5zmtps7zmtps44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb071070 Gene Symbol: D5 ZmTPS7 ZmTPS44 Gene Name: dwarf plant 5|terpene synthase 7 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRO1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26840/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26840/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g26840 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0439800 Gene Symbol: DRO1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaJAZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cotton_A_11862 Gene Symbol: GaJAZ1 Gene Name: Genome: Gossypium hirsutum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhAPX</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghapx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghapx/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: GhAPX Gene Name: Genome: Cotton Genome Database Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Root growth of GhAPX-overexpressing Arabidopsis subjected to abiotic stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCERP</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcerp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcerp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D02G2021 Gene Symbol: GhCERP Gene Name: Genome: cotton genome (Gossypium hirsutum, NAU) Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Inter-species functional analysis of the BR-mediated BES1-CERP-EXPA3 signaling cascade also promotes Arabidopsis root and hypocotyl growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhEXPA3-1</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghexpa3-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghexpa3-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D04G1924 Gene Symbol: GhEXPA3-1 Gene Name: Genome: cotton genome (Gossypium hirsutum, NAU) Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhBES1 directly binds to E-box of GhCERP and regulates the transcription of GhCERP, which further binds to E-box of GhEXPA3-1 to enhance its transcription to promote plant cell elongation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMKK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhMKK3 Gene Name: Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase Kinase 3 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase Kinase 3 (GhMKK3) Functions in Drought Tolerance by Regulating Stomatal Responses and Root Growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhWRKY17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhWRKY17 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 17 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton WRKY Transcription Factor GhWRKY17 Functions in Drought and Salt Stress in Transgenic Nicotiana benthamiana Through ABA Signaling and the Modulation of Reactive Oxygen Species Production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmALMT5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.02g147900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.02g147900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.02g147900 Gene Symbol: GmALMT5 Gene Name: aluminum-activated malate transporter 5 Genome: Wm82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmERF75</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.10g016500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.10g016500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.10G016500 Gene Symbol: GmERF75 Gene Name: Ethylene-responsive factor gene 75 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The ABA-induced soybean ERF transcription factor gene GmERF75 plays a role in enhancing osmotic stress tolerance in Arabidopsis and soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmETO1</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmeto1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmeto1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.14G197100 Gene Symbol: GmETO1 Gene Name: Ethylene-Overproduction Protein 1 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Up-regulating GmETO1 improves phosphorus uptake and use efficiency by promoting root growth in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmEXPB2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmexpb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmexpb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmEXPB2 Gene Name: β-expansin gene Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmEXPB2, a Cell Wall β-Expansin, Affects Soybean Nodulation through Modifying Root Architecture and Promoting Nodule Formation and Development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmMYB84</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.05g234600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.05g234600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.05G234600 Gene Symbol: GmMYB84 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB Transcription Factor 84 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Drought Tolerance Conferred in Soybean (Glycine max.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmNMH7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmnmh7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmnmh7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmNMH7 Gene Name: Nodule MADS-box Homologue 7 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: In situ expression of the GmNMH7 gene is photoperiod-dependent in a unique soybean (Glycine max [L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmNPLa</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmnpla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmnpla/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.11G244800 Gene Symbol: GmNPLa Gene Name: phosphate starvation-induced transcription factor 1 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmNPLa was specifically induced by rhizobium inoculation in root hairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPHR25</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.15g123100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.15g123100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.15g123100 Gene Symbol: GmPHR25 Gene Name: PHOSPHATE STARVATION RESPONSE 25 Genome: Wm82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPIP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g015300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g015300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.08g015300 Gene Symbol: GmPIP1|6 Gene Name: plasma membrane intrinsic protein 1|6 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The effects of constitutive overexpression of GmPIP1|6|GmPIP1|6 in soybean was examined under normal and salt stress conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRR1</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmrr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmrr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.09g040000 Gene Symbol: GmRR1 Gene Name: a soybean type-B Response Regulator 1 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Soybean type-B response regulator GmRR1 mediates phosphorus uptake and yield by modifying root architecture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSALT3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g32900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma03g32900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma03g32900 Gene Symbol: GmSALT3 Gene Name: cation-proton exchanger protein Genome: Wm82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSAP5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/gmsap5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/gmsap5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmSAP5 Gene Name: Stress-associated proteins Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmSAP5, a soybean A20/AN1 domain-containing stress-associated protein gene activated by GmAREB3, increases drought stress resistance in soybean by mediating ABA signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmYSL7</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmysl7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmysl7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.11G203400 Gene Symbol: GmYSL7 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmYSL7 controls iron uptake, allocation, and cellular response of nodules in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmYUC2a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g038600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g038600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.08g038600 Gene Symbol: GmYUC2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmYUC2a mediates auxin biosynthesis during root development and nodulation in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmYUC2a</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmyuc2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmyuc2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.08g038600 Gene Symbol: GmYUC2a Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: We analyzed the YUCCA (YUC) gene family of soybean and identified GmYUC2a as an important regulator of auxin biosynthesis that modulates nodulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCslF3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/horvu2hr1g042350/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/horvu2hr1g042350/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU2Hr1G042350 Gene Symbol: HvCslF3 Gene Name: cellulose synthase-like F3 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: The cellulose synthase-like F3 (HvCslF3) gene mediates cell wall polysaccharide synthesis and affects root growth and differentiation in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvEXPB7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvEXPB7 Gene Name: β-expansin gene Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvEXPB7, a novel β-expansin gene revealed by the root hair transcriptome of Tibetan wild barley, improves root hair growth under drought stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNPF2.12</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g092870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g092870/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU3Hr1G092870 Gene Symbol: HvNPF2.12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Convergently selected NPF2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVP10</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G028910 Gene Symbol: HVP10 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: This study reveals the molecular mechanism of HVP10 underlying salt tolerance and highlights its potential in improving crop salt tolerance Vacuolar H+-pyrophosphatase HVP10 enhances salt tolerance via promoting Na+ translocation into root vacuoles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvRAF</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvraf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvraf/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvRAF Gene Name: root abundant factor Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The barley ERF-type transcription factor HvRAF confers enhanced pathogen resistance and salt tolerance in Arabidopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbEXP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibexp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibexp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbEXP1 Gene Name: expansin gene Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: The expressions of IbEXP1, IbEXP2 and IbEXPL1 were significantly correlated with the changes in cell wall component content, and were related to the qualitative structure changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbMYB73</title>
      <link>/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibmyb73/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibmyb73/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;itb01g33150.t1 Gene Symbol: IbMYB73 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: IbMYB73 targets abscisic acid-responsive IbGER5 to regulate root growth and stress tolerance in sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbNAC1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibnac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibnac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: IbNAC1 was constitutively expressed in root tissues and was induced earlier than sporamin following the wounding of leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbVP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibvp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibvp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbVP1 Gene Name: H+-pyrophosphatase 1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: H+-pyrophosphatase IbVP1 promotes efficient iron use in sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaCLE35</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0213851/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0213851/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lalb_Chr05g0213851 Gene Symbol: LaCLE35 Gene Name: Genome: Species: lupinus albus Functional Descriptions: The LaCLE35 peptide modifies rootlet density and length in cluster roots of white lupin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBL1;rgd1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/lbl1rgd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/lbl1rgd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb264310 Gene Symbol: LBL1 rgd1 Gene Name: ragged seedling1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjCCD7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsga_131670.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsga_131670.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: LjSGA_131670.1 Gene Symbol: LjCCD7 Gene Name: CAROTENOID CLEAVAGE DIOXYGENASE 7 Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: CAROTENOID CLEAVAGE DIOXYGENASE 7 modulates plant growth, reproduction, senescence, and determinate nodulation in the model legume Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjMAMI</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljmami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljmami/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjMAMI Gene Name: MYB-like transcription factor Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: An AM-induced, MYB-family gene of Lotus japonicus (LjMAMI) affects root growth in an AM-independent manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjSYP132b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lotja-gi3g-1v0190600.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lotja-gi3g-1v0190600.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lotja Gi3g 1v0190600.1 Gene Symbol: LjSYP132b Gene Name: Genome: L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjSYP32-1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsyp32-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsyp32-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjSYP32-1 Gene Name: Sed5 -like SNARE Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: We identified a Sed5 -like clone LjSYP32-1 which contributes to nodule tissue formation and plant growth in Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LRD</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/lrd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/lrd/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7D02G501000 Gene Symbol: LRD Gene Name: LATERAL ROOT DENSITY Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBPC2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbpc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbpc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD16G1012800 Gene Symbol: MdBPC2 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdHT1.2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdht1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdht1.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD10G1304000 Gene Symbol: MdHT1.2 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica GDDH13 v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHZ11</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g11950/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g11950/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g11950 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0210100 Gene Symbol: MHZ11 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>miR444</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/mir444/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/mir444/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: None RAPdb gene ID: None Gene Symbol: miR444 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsDHN1</title>
      <link>/genes/medicago_sativa/msdhn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/medicago_sativa/msdhn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsDHN1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results indicate that MsDHN1 can increase alfalfa tolerance to Al stress via increasing oxalate secretion from root tips, which may involve in the interaction of MsDHN1 with two AQP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsDREB6.2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-sieversii/msdreb6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-sieversii/msdreb6.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MsDREB6.2 Gene Name: Dehydration-responsive element binding factor 6 Genome: apple sequence database (http://genomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtbHLH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtbhlh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtbhlh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtbHLH1 Gene Name: basic helix loop helix 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: MtbHLH1, a bHLH transcription factor involved in Medicago truncatula nodule vascular patterning and nodule to plant metabolic exchanges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCLE12</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g079630/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g079630/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g079630 Gene Symbol: MtCLE12 Gene Name: CLAVATA3/ESR (CLE)-related protein 12 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Root growth inhibition was detected when MtCLE12 was ectopically expressed in wild-type roots or synthetic CLE12 peptide was applied exogenously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtMOT1.2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtMOT1.2 Gene Name: Molybdate Transporter 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNAC969</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnac969/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnac969/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtNAC969 Gene Name: NAC969 transcription factor Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Over-expression of one of these transcription factors, MtNAC969, induced formation of a shorter and less-branched root system, whereas RNAi-mediated MtNAC969 inactivation promoted lateral root formation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNFH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g116990.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g116990.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g116990.1 Gene Symbol: MtNFH1|MtChit5 Gene Name: NOD FACTOR HYDROLASE1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Role of the Nod Factor Hydrolase MtNFH1|MtChit5 in Regulating Nod Factor Levels during Rhizobial Infection and in Mature Nodules of Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtROP9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtROP9 Gene Name: small G-protein ROP9 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the Rac1 GTPase MtROP9 in Medicago truncatula Stimulates Early Mycorrhizal and Oomycete Root Colonizations But Negatively Affects Rhizobial Infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtRopGEF2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g030850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g030850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g030850 Gene Symbol: MtRopGEF2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Phosphorylation of MtRopGEF2 by LYK3 mediates MtROP activity to regulate rhizobial infection in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtYSL7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g063490/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g063490/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g063490 Gene Symbol: MtYSL7 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRabE1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRabE1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: We characterized the gene expression, subcellular localization, and in vivo functions of a Nicotiana benthamiana small GTPase belonging to the RabE family, designated NbRabE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtGNL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtGNL1 Gene Name: GNOM-like 1 protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtGNL1 is involved in embryonic cell division patterning, root elongation, and pollen tube growth in tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtPDR3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntpdr3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntpdr3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtPDR3 Gene Name: pleiotropic drug resistance protein 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The Nicotiana tabacum ABC transporter NtPDR3 secretes O-methylated coumarins in response to iron deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsBZR1;BZR1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g39220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g39220/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g39220 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0580500 Gene Symbol: OsBZR1 BZR1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCCA1;Nhd1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g06110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g06110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g06110 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0157600 Gene Symbol: OsCCA1 Nhd1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCML16</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g04330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g04330/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g04330 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0135700 Gene Symbol: OsCML16 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCOI1;OsCOI1a</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g63420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g63420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g63420 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0853400 Gene Symbol: OsCOI1 OsCOI1a Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCOI1b</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g37690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g37690/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g37690 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0449500 Gene Symbol: OsCOI1b Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCOI2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g15880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g15880/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g15880 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0265500 Gene Symbol: OsCOI2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsERA1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g53600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g53600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g53600 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0737800 Gene Symbol: OsERA1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsERF106MZ</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/oserf106mz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/oserf106mz/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: None RAPdb gene ID: None Gene Symbol: OsERF106MZ Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsJAZ9;OsTIFY11a</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g08310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g08310/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g08310 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0180800 Gene Symbol: OsJAZ9 OsTIFY11a Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMADS27</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g36924/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g36924/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g36924 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0579600 Gene Symbol: OsMADS27 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMGD3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g20420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g20420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g20420 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0299400 Gene Symbol: OsMGD3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMKK1;OsMEK2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g05520/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g05520/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g05520 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0147800 Gene Symbol: OsMKK1 OsMEK2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMYB58;OsMYB63</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g50770/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g50770/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g50770 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0594100 Gene Symbol: OsMYB58 OsMYB63 RRS1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsNAR2.2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g40410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g40410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g40410 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0480200 Gene Symbol: OsNAR2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsNIT1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42350/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42350/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g42350 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0635200 Gene Symbol: OsNIT1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsNIT2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g42330/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g42330 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0635000 Gene Symbol: OsNIT2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsNMCP1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g48010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g48010/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g48010 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0709900 ,Os02g0710102 Gene Symbol: OsNMCP1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPEX1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g43640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g43640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g43640 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0657400 Gene Symbol: OsPEX1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPIN3t</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g45550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g45550/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g45550 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0643300 Gene Symbol: OsPIN3t Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsrbohB;Osrboh7</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26660/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g26660 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0438000 Gene Symbol: OsrbohB Osrboh7 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRbohI</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g33120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g33120/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g33120 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0537400 Gene Symbol: OsRbohI Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsRPT4</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g10640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g10640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g10640 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0199900 Gene Symbol: OsRPT4 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSQD1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g32140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g32140/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g32140 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0387200 Gene Symbol: OsSQD1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSWI3C;OsCHB705</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g08080/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g08080/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g08080 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0183700 Gene Symbol: OsSWI3C OsCHB705 CHB705 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PdGNC</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.006g229200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.006g229200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Potri.006G229200 Gene Symbol: PdGNC Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus trichocarpa Functional Descriptions: The GATA transcription factor GNC (PdGNC) plays an important role in photosynthesis and growth in poplar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtPHOR1_1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/poptr_0007s03730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/poptr_0007s03730/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: POPTR_0007s03730 Gene Symbol: PtPHOR1_1 Gene Name: PHOTOPERIOD RESPONSE 1 Genome: Species: Populus tremula x Populus alba Functional Descriptions: PHOTOPERIOD RESPONSE 1 (PHOR1)-like Genes Regulate Shoot/root Growth, Starch Accumulation, and Wood Formation in Populus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtPHOR1_2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/poptr_0005s05880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-tremula-x-populus-alba/poptr_0005s05880/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: POPTR_0005s05880 Gene Symbol: PtPHOR1_2 Gene Name: PHOTOPERIOD RESPONSE 1 Genome: Species: Populus tremula x Populus alba Functional Descriptions: PHOTOPERIOD RESPONSE 1 (PHOR1)-like Genes Regulate Shoot/root Growth, Starch Accumulation, and Wood Formation in Populus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuHox52</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-ussuriensis/puhox52/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-ussuriensis/puhox52/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuHox52 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: PuHox52 promotes coordinated uptake of nitrate, phosphate, and iron under nitrogen deficiency in Populus ussuriensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>qSOR1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42290/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42290/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g42290 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0614400 Gene Symbol: qSOR1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTH1;ZmRTH1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/rth1zmrth1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/rth1zmrth1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb051220 Gene Symbol: RTH1 ZmRTH1 Gene Name: roothairless 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTH3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/rth3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/rth3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb014120 Gene Symbol: RTH3 Gene Name: roothairless 3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTH6</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/rth6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/rth6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb025100 Gene Symbol: RTH6 Gene Name: roothairless 6 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SaVHAc1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/spartina-alterniflora/savhac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/spartina-alterniflora/savhac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SaVHAc1 Gene Name: vacuolar ATPase subunit c1 Genome: Species: Spartina alterniflora Functional Descriptions: Enhanced salt stress tolerance of rice plants expressing a vacuolar H+-ATPase subunit c1 (SaVHAc1) gene from the halophyte grass Spartina alterniflora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SbMATE</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sb03g043890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sb03g043890/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sb03g043890 Gene Symbol: SbMATE Gene Name: multi-drug and toxic compound extrusion Genome: Species: Sorghum bicolor Functional Descriptions: Sugarcane plants constitutively overexpressing the Sorghum bicolor MATE gene (SbMATE) showed improved tolerance to Al when compared to non-transgenic (NT) plants, characterized by sustained root growth and exclusion of aluminum from the root apex based on the result obtained with hematoxylin staining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SbPSTOL1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sb03g006765/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sb03g006765/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sb03g006765 Gene Symbol: SbPSTOL1 Gene Name: PHOSPHORUS-STARVATION TOLERANCE1 Genome: Species: Sorghum bicolor Functional Descriptions: SbPSTOL1 genes colocalized with quantitative trait loci for traits underlying root morphology and dry weight accumulation under low P via linkage mapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlCyp1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slcyp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slcyp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlCyp1 Gene Name: low-temperature-induced cysteine proteinase Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Here, we show that, in tomato, translocation of a phloem-mobile cyclophilin, SlCyp1, from a wild-type scion into a mutant rootstock results in restoration of vascular development and lateral root initiation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLGlyI</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slglyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slglyi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc09g082120.3.1 Gene Symbol: SLGlyI Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPYL9</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slpyl9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slpyl9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc09g015380 Gene Symbol: SlPYL9 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlUGT75C1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g092500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g092500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc09g092500 Gene Symbol: SlUGT75C1 Gene Name: UDP-glycosyltransferase 75C1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlUGT75C1 catalyzes the glucosylation of both ABA and IAA in vitro| SlUGT76E1 can only catalyze the conjugation of ABA| and SlUGT73C4 cannot glycosylate either ABA or IAA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabHLH27-A1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g271700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2a02g271700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2A02G271700 Gene Symbol: TabHLH27-A1 Gene Name: basic helix-loop-helix transcription factor 27 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TabHLH27 orchestrates root growth and drought tolerance to enhance water use efficiency in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabHLH27-B1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g289900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b02g289900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2B02G289900 Gene Symbol: TabHLH27-B1 Gene Name: basic helix-loop-helix transcription factor 27 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TabHLH27 orchestrates root growth and drought tolerance to enhance water use efficiency in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabHLH27-D1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g270300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2d02g270300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2D02G270300 Gene Symbol: TabHLH27-D1 Gene Name: basic helix-loop-helix transcription factor 27 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TabHLH27 orchestrates root growth and drought tolerance to enhance water use efficiency in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabZIP60</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tabzip60/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tabzip60/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: TabZIP60 Gene Name: basic leucine zipper transcription factor 60 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaFMO1-5B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafmo1-5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafmo1-5b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5B02G350700 Gene Symbol: TaFMO1-5B Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGS2-2Aa</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2aa/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaGS2-2Aa Gene Name: glutamine synthetase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic expression of TaGS2-2Ab significantly increased GS2 abundance and GS activity in leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGS2-2Ab</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2ab/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaGS2-2Ab Gene Name: glutamine synthetase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic expression of TaGS2-2Ab significantly increased GS2 abundance and GS activity in leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMADS2-3D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamads2-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tamads2-3d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS3D02G428000 Gene Symbol: TaMADS2-3D Gene Name: MADS-box transcription factor 2 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNAC14</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanac14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanac14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS2A02G338300 Gene Symbol: TaNAC14 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNAC2-5A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanac2-5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanac2-5a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaNAC2-5A Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Nitrate-Inducible NAC Transcription Factor TaNAC2-5A Controls Nitrate Response and Increases Wheat Yield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNOX7-3A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanox7-3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tanox7-3a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: TaNOX7-3A Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNPF2.12</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3b02g454100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3b02g454100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3B02G454100 Gene Symbol: TaNPF2.12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Convergently selected NPF2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaNRT2.1-6B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs6b02g044300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs6b02g044300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS6B02G044300 Gene Symbol: TaNRT2.1-6B Gene Name: NITRATE TRANSPORTER 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The data provide the TaNRT2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaOPR1</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taopr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taopr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaOPR1 Gene Name: Oxophytodienoate Reductase 1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat Oxophytodienoate Reductase Gene TaOPR1 Confers Salinity Tolerance via Enhancement of Abscisic Acid Signaling and Reactive Oxygen Species Scavenging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaOPR3</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taopr3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taopr3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7A03G0999600 Gene Symbol: TaOPR3 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSINA1D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs1d03g0330200-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs1d03g0330200-/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS1D03G0330200 Gene Symbol: TaSINA1D Gene Name: SINA-type E3 Ub ligase Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaSINA1D-OE transgenic wheat lines showed similar drought tolerance and root growth phenotype to those observed when TaSINA2B was overexpressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSINA2B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b03g0366300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs2b03g0366300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2B03G0366300 Gene Symbol: TaSINA2B Gene Name: SINA-type E3 Ub ligase Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaSINA2B, interacting with TaSINA1D, positively regulates drought tolerance and root growth in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4A02G005600 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4A Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4B02G299400 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4B Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4D02G298400 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4D Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaTAR2.1-3A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tatar2.1-3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tatar2.1-3a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaTAR2.1-3A Gene Name: RYPTOPHAN AMINOTRANSFERASE RELATED Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Auxin Biosynthetic TRYPTOPHAN AMINOTRANSFERASE RELATED TaTAR2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOX11</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g48560/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g48560/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g48560 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0684900 Gene Symbol: WOX11 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmABA2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb212270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb212270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb212270 Gene Symbol: ZmABA2|sca1 Gene Name: short chain alcohol dehydrogenase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmACS7</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmacs7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmacs7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb428490 Gene Symbol: ZmACS7 Gene Name: 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate synthase7 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmATR</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmatr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmatr/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb228310 Gene Symbol: ZmATR Gene Name: ataxia-telangiectasia mutated and RAD3-related1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAUX1;atl1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmaux1atl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmaux1atl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb147480 Gene Symbol: ZmAUX1 atl1 Gene Name: auxin transporter-like1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAuxRP1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmauxrp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmauxrp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb053610 Gene Symbol: ZmAuxRP1 Gene Name: auxin-regulated protein1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmBET5L1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmbet5l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmbet5l1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb217960 Gene Symbol: ZmBET5L1 Gene Name: BET5-like1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmbZIP4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb255970 Gene Symbol: ZmbZIP4 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCEP1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmcep1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmcep1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb038200 Gene Symbol: ZmCEP1 Gene Name: C-terminally encoded peptide1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCIPK15</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmcipk15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmcipk15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb051020 Gene Symbol: ZmCIPK15 Gene Name: calcineurin B-like-interacting protein kinase4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCIPK3;ZmSnRK3.2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmcipk3zmsnrk3.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmcipk3zmsnrk3.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb015210 Gene Symbol: ZmCIPK3 ZmSnRK3.2 Gene Name: calcineurin B-like-interacting protein kinase3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmDRO1;ZmLAZY1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmdro1zmlazy1dro1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmdro1zmlazy1dro1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb314060 Gene Symbol: ZmDRO1 ZmLAZY1 DRO1 Gene Name: deeper rooting1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmEXPB4;EXPB4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmexpb4expb4expb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmexpb4expb4expb17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb391450 Gene Symbol: ZmEXPB4 EXPB4 expb17 Gene Name: beta expansin17 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmHB133;RLD1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmhb133rld1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmhb133rld1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb404260 Gene Symbol: ZmHB133 RLD1 Gene Name: rolled leaf1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmHB58;RLD2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmhb58rld2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmhb58rld2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb000690 Gene Symbol: ZmHB58 RLD2 Gene Name: rolled leaf2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmIAA5;ZmIAA10</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmiaa5zmiaa10rum1iaa13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmiaa5zmiaa10rum1iaa13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb156910 Gene Symbol: ZmIAA5 ZmIAA10 rum1 iaa13 Gene Name: rootless with undetectable meristems1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmLRL5;lrl5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmlrl5lrl5bhlh10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmlrl5lrl5bhlh10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb374700 Gene Symbol: ZmLRL5 lrl5 bhlh10 Gene Name: bHLH-transcription factor 10 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMYB81;myb81</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmmyb81myb81/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmmyb81myb81/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb124630 Gene Symbol: ZmMYB81 myb81 Gene Name: MYB-transcription factor 81 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNF-YA1;nfya1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya1nfya1ca2p11zmnfya01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnf-ya1nfya1ca2p11zmnfya01/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb005690 Gene Symbol: ZmNF-YA1 nfya1 ca2p11 ZmNFYA01 Gene Name: nuclear transcription factor y subunit a1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNRAMP2;nrat3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnramp2nrat3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnramp2nrat3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb400560 Gene Symbol: ZmNRAMP2 nrat3 Gene Name: nramp aluminum transporter3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmPP2AA1;prh17</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmpp2aa1prh17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmpp2aa1prh17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb269610 Gene Symbol: ZmPP2AA1 prh17 Gene Name: protein phosphatase homolog17 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmPTF1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmptf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmptf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GRMZM2G024530 Gene Symbol: ZmPTF1 Gene Name: Pi starvation-induced transcription factor1 Genome: B73_RefGen_v3 Species: Zea mays Functional Descriptions: ZmPTF1, a phosphate starvation-induced basic helix-loop-helix (bHLH) transcription factor, contributes to root development and low-phosphate tolerance in maize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRALF12;ralf12</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmralf12ralf12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmralf12ralf12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb410350 Gene Symbol: ZmRALF12 ralf12 Gene Name: rapid alkalinization factor12 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSLAH2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmslah2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmslah2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb358580 Gene Symbol: ZmSLAH2 Gene Name: Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmTMM1;mads26</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmtmm1mads26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmtmm1mads26/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb253580 Gene Symbol: ZmTMM1 mads26 Gene Name: MADS-transcription factor 26 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmVPP1;vpp5</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmvpp1vpp5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmvpp1vpp5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb387010 Gene Symbol: ZmVPP1 vpp5 Gene Name: vacuolar-type H+-pyrophosphatase5 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
