<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>growth rate on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/growth-rate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in growth rate on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/growth-rate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BplncSIR1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bplncsir1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bplncsir1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BplncSIR1 Gene Name: salt-responsive nuclear lncRNA Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Birch plants overexpressing and knocking out for BplncSIR1 were generated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BramMDH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/bra039662/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/bra039662/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bra039662 Gene Symbol: BramMDH1 Gene Name: mitochondrial malate dehydrogenase 1 Genome: Brassica database (http://brassicadb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSR2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g43390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g43390/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g43390 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0547300 Gene Symbol: BSR2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSEF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssef1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssef1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSEF1 Gene Name: putative CCCH-type zinc finger protein Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Expression of CsSEF1 gene encoding putative CCCH zinc finger protein is induced by defoliation and prolonged darkness in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsYUC10b</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyuc10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyuc10b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G190380 Gene Symbol: CsYUC10b Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsYUC10b promotes the formation of straight cucumber fruits, with possible applications in the production and breeding of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghd7</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g15770/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g15770/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g15770 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0261200 Gene Symbol: Ghd7 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhWRKY17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhWRKY17 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 17 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton WRKY Transcription Factor GhWRKY17 Functions in Drought and Salt Stress in Transgenic Nicotiana benthamiana Through ABA Signaling and the Modulation of Reactive Oxygen Species Production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmMYB84</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.05g234600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.05g234600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.05G234600 Gene Symbol: GmMYB84 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB Transcription Factor 84 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Drought Tolerance Conferred in Soybean (Glycine max.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVP10</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G028910 Gene Symbol: HVP10 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: This study reveals the molecular mechanism of HVP10 underlying salt tolerance and highlights its potential in improving crop salt tolerance Vacuolar H+-pyrophosphatase HVP10 enhances salt tolerance via promoting Na+ translocation into root vacuoles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOC2;FBP1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g64660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g64660/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g64660 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0866400 Gene Symbol: MOC2 FBP1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPHR3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g04640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g04640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g04640 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0139000 Gene Symbol: OsPHR3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZT1;OsMTP1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g03780/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g03780/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g03780 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0128400 Gene Symbol: OZT1 OsMTP1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PagLBD3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-alba-populus-glandulosa/potri.008g043900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-alba-populus-glandulosa/potri.008g043900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Potri.008G043900 Gene Symbol: PagLBD3 Gene Name: LATERAL ORGAN BOUNDARIES DOMAIN 3 Genome: Populus trichocarpa v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PdGNC</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.006g229200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.006g229200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Potri.006G229200 Gene Symbol: PdGNC Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus trichocarpa Functional Descriptions: The GATA transcription factor GNC (PdGNC) plays an important role in photosynthesis and growth in poplar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl-STIG1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl-stig1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl-stig1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Sl-STIG1 Gene Name: STIGMA-SPECIFIC PROTEIN1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato Pistil Factor STIG1 Promotes in Vivo Pollen Tube Growth by Binding to Phosphatidylinositol 3-Phosphate and the Extracellular Domain of the Pollen Receptor Kinase LePRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGS2-2Aa</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2aa/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaGS2-2Aa Gene Name: glutamine synthetase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic expression of TaGS2-2Ab significantly increased GS2 abundance and GS activity in leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGS2-2Ab</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tags2-2ab/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaGS2-2Ab Gene Name: glutamine synthetase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Transgenic expression of TaGS2-2Ab significantly increased GS2 abundance and GS activity in leaves.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
