<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>transcriptional repressor on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/transcriptional-repressor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in transcriptional repressor on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/transcriptional-repressor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CaARF9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana00g000236/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana00g000236/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana00g000236 Gene Symbol: CaARF9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Demonstrate that an auxin response factor, CaARF9, has dual roles in enhancing the immune resistance to Ralstonia solanacearum infection and in retarding plant growth by repressing the expression of its target genes as exemplified by Casmc4, CaLBD37, CaAPK1b and CaRROP1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClNAC68</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C03G059250 Gene Symbol: ClNAC68 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: The NAC transcription factor ClNAC68 positively regulates sugar content and seed development in watermelon by repressing ClINV and ClGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmBBX22</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cs3_sc004370.1_g0600.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cs3_sc004370.1_g0600.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs3_sc004370.1_g0600.1 Gene Symbol: CmBBX22 Gene Name: BBX transcription factor 22 Genome: Chrysanthemum seticuspe genome release CSE_r1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmMYB121</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/unigene68526-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/unigene68526-all/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Unigene68526-All Gene Symbol: CmMYB121 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 121 Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CmHSFA4-CmMYBS3 complex enhances salt tolerance in chrysanthemum by repressing CmMYB121 expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmMYB44</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmmyb44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmmyb44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MELO3C016789 Gene Symbol: CmMYB44 Gene Name: MYB44 transcription factor Genome: Melon (DHL92) v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmMYBS3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmmybs3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmmybs3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmMYBS3 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor S3 Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Protein–protein interaction assays identified an interaction between CmHSFA4 and CmMYBS3, a transcriptional repressor, and recruited the corepressor TOPLESS (CmTPL) to inhibit CmMYB121 transcription by impairing the H3 and H4 histone acetylation levels of CmMYB121.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmSVP</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmsvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmsvp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: evm. TU. Scaffold_5250.69 Gene Symbol: CmSVP Gene Name: SHORT VEGETATIVE PHASE Genome: Chrysanthemum Genome Database (http://210.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmWRKY15-like</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmwrky15-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmwrky15-like/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmWRKY15-like Gene Name: Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: Isolated CmWRKY6–1 from chrysanthemum ‘Jinba’ and identified it as a transcriptional repressor localized in the nucleus via subcellular localization and transcriptional activation assays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAP2L1</title>
      <link>/genes/cannabis_sativa/csap2l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cannabis_sativa/csap2l1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsAP2L1 Gene Name: CsAP2-Like1 Genome: Species: Cannabis Sativa Functional Description: CsAP2L1 playing a positive role in the regulation of THCAS expression, while CsWRKY1 and CsMYB1 may serve as negative regulators of THCAS expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMYB14</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMYB14 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMYB14 is a bifunctional transcription factor that regulates the accumulation of proanthocyanidin in persimmon fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghir_D05G01221</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghir_d05g01221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghir_d05g01221/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ghir_D05G01221 Gene Symbol: Ghir_D05G01221 Gene Name: Genome: G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWRKY1</title>
      <link>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvWRKY1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvWRKY1 is phosphorylated in barley at the early stages of Bgh infection, which enhances its suppression on barley immunity likely due to enhanced DNA-binding and transcriptional repression activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeSPL-CNR</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lespl-cnr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lespl-cnr/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeSPL-CNR Gene Name: SQUAMOSA PROMOTER-BINDING PROTEIN-LIKE Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: LeSPL-CNR negatively regulates Cd acquisition through repressing nitrate reductase-mediated nitric oxide production in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjbHLH7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lj0g3v0343449/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lj0g3v0343449/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lj0g3v0343449 Gene Symbol: LjbHLH7 Gene Name: MeJA-responsive bHLH transcription factor Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: MeJA-responsive bHLH transcription factor LjbHLH7 regulates cyanogenic glucoside biosynthesis in Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjJAZ4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lj4g3v2215580/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/lj4g3v2215580/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lj4g3v2215580 Gene Symbol: LjJAZ4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: The transcriptional activity of LjbHLH7 was suppressed by the interaction with the L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LsAP2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lsap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lsap2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LsAP2 Gene Name: APETALA2 Genome: Species: Lactuca sativa Functional Descriptions: The lettuce APETALA2 (LsAP2) gene regulates leaf morphology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaDof23</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr11t03360_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr11t03360_001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GSMUA_Achr11T03360_001 Gene Symbol: MaDof23 Gene Name: Putative Dof zinc finger protein DOF4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaDREB2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr5g28050_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr5g28050_001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GSMUA_Achr5G28050_001 Gene Symbol: MaDREB2 Gene Name: dehydration-responsive element binding 2 Genome: The Banana Genome Hub (http://banana-genome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMYB16L</title>
      <link>/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb16l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb16l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MaMYB16L Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: The alternative splicing of MaMYB16L might generate a self-controlled regulatory loop to regulate banana fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdARF5-1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdarf5-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdarf5-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000143749 Gene Symbol: MdARF5-1 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBEL7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbel7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbel7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdBEL7 Gene Name: BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 7 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: An apple (Malus domestica) BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 7 (MdBEL7), potentially functioning as a transcriptional repressor of the Chl catabolic genes (CCGs), including MdCLH, MdPPH2 and MdRCCR2, was identified as a partner of the ethylene-activated U-box type E3 ubiquitin ligase MdPUB24 in a yeast library screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdbHLH162</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/md09g1233000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/md09g1233000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD09G1233000 Gene Symbol: MdbHLH162 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdbHLH162 connects the gibberellin and jasmonic acid signals to regulate anthocyanin biosynthesis in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdIAA29</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdiaa29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdiaa29/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MDP0000543718 Gene Symbol: MdIAA29 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000237742/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000237742 Gene Symbol: MdMAPK3 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 3 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Ethylene enhances MdMAPK3-mediated phosphorylation of MdNAC72 to promote apple fruit softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdNAC72</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdnac72/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdnac72/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdNAC72 Gene Name: transcription factor NAM-ATAF1/2-CUC2 72 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor NAM-ATAF1/2-CUC2 72 (MdNAC72), which functions as a transcriptional repressor of the cell wall degradation-related gene POLYGALACTURONASE1 (MdPG1).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeHDZ14</title>
      <link>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mehdz14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/manihot_esculenta/mehdz14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Manes.01G242300 Gene Symbol: MeHDZ14 Gene Name: Genome: Manihot esculenta, v8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGT1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g22020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g22020/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g22020 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0325600 Gene Symbol: NIGT1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsARF18;RST1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g47150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g47150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g47150 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0685700 Gene Symbol: OsARF18 RST1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCCT38;OsPRR59</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g05930/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g05930/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g05930 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0157600 Gene Symbol: OsCCT38 OsPRR59 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsERF115;AP2EREBP110</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g41030/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g41030/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g41030 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0521600 Gene Symbol: OsERF115 AP2EREBP110 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMGT3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g48000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g48000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g48000 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0684400 Gene Symbol: OsMGT3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMYB7</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g37210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g37210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g37210 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0558100 Gene Symbol: OsMYB7 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPRR95</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g36220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g36220/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g36220 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0532400 Gene Symbol: OsPRR95 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWRKY10</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g09100 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0186000 Gene Symbol: OsWRKY10 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsWRKY62</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g25070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g25070/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g25070 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0417800 Gene Symbol: OsWRKY62 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpERF105</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pperf105/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pperf105/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PpERF105 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-activated PpERF105 induces the expression of the repressor-type R2R3-MYB gene PpMYB140 to inhibit anthocyanin biosynthesis in red pear fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpMYB140</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pbr000876.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pbr000876.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pbr000876.1 Gene Symbol: PpMYB140 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-activated PpERF105 induces the expression of the repressor-type R2R3-MYB gene PpMYB140 to inhibit anthocyanin biosynthesis in red pear fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ra1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/ra1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/ra1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb312340 Gene Symbol: Ra1 Gene Name: ramosa1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhPLATZ9</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhplatz9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhplatz9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhPLATZ9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The RhWRKY33a-RhPLATZ9 regulatory module delays petal senescence by suppressing rapid reactive oxygen species accumulation in rose flowers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhWRKY33a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhwrky33a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhwrky33a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhWRKY33a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The RhWRKY33a-RhPLATZ9 regulatory module delays petal senescence by suppressing rapid reactive oxygen species accumulation in rose flowers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl-ERF.B3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g052030/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g052030/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc05g052030 Gene Symbol: Sl-ERF.B3 Gene Name: Ethylene Response Factor Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The chimeric repressor version of an Ethylene Response Factor (ERF) family member, Sl-ERF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl-IAA17</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl-iaa17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sl-iaa17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Sl-IAA17 Gene Name: auxin/indole acetic acid 17 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The Auxin Sl-IAA17 Transcriptional Repressor Controls Fruit Size Via the Regulation of Endoreduplication-Related Cell Expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAP2c</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g093150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g093150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g093150 Gene Symbol: SlAP2c Gene Name: APETALA2 transcription factor Genome: ITAG4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlBES1.8</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbes1.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slbes1.8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc10g076390 Gene Symbol: SlBES1.8 Gene Name: Brassinazole-resistant 1 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlIAA15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/sliaa15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/sliaa15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlIAA15 Gene Name: Auxin-responsive protein Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The tomato SlIAA15 is involved in trichome formation and axillary shoot development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlWUS</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slwus/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc02g083950 Gene Symbol: SlWUS Gene Name: WUSCHEL Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SS1;ONAC025</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g31330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g31330/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g31330 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0512000 Gene Symbol: SS1 ONAC025 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAM1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g47590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g47590/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi2g47590 Gene Symbol: SWAM1 Gene Name: SECONDARY WALL ASSOCIATED MYB1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: SWAM1 overexpression (SWAM-OE) lines had greater above-ground biomass with only a slight change in flowering time while SWAM1 dominant repressor (SWAM1-DR) plants were severely dwarfed with a striking reduction in lignin of sclerenchyma fibers and stem epidermal cell length.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TPL4</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/tpl4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/tpl4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD04G1197000 Gene Symbol: TPL4 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAFB1;tir1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmafb1tir1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmafb1tir1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb354200 Gene Symbol: ZmAFB1 tir1 Gene Name: transport inhibitor response1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmEREB179</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb006160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb006160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb006160 Gene Symbol: ZmEREB179 Gene Name: AP2-EREBP transcription factor 179 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMS1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb272570/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb272570/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb272570 Gene Symbol: ZmMS1|ZmLBD30 Gene Name: male sterile1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
