<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fatty acid on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/fatty-acid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fatty acid on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/fatty-acid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BnFAX6</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/bnfax6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/bnfax6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;BnaC05G0364600WE Gene Symbol: BnFAX6 Gene Name: Fatty Acid Export 6 Genome: ZS11 reference genome Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Fatty acid export protein BnFAX6 functions in lipid synthesis and axillary bud growth in Brassica napus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnWRI1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bnwri1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bnwri1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnWRI1 Gene Name: AP2/EREBP transcription factor Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: BnWRI1 coordinates fatty acid biosynthesis and photosynthesis pathways during oil accumulation in rapeseed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAD2-1A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma10g42470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma10g42470/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma10g42470 Gene Symbol: FAD2-1A Gene Name: omega-6 fatty acid desaturase Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Mutant alleles of FAD2-1A and FAD2-1Bcombine to produce soybeans with the high oleic acid seed oil trait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAD2-1B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma20g24530/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma20g24530/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma20g24530 Gene Symbol: FAD2-1B Gene Name: omega-6 fatty acid desaturase Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Mutant alleles of FAD2-1A and FAD2-1Bcombine to produce soybeans with the high oleic acid seed oil trait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhACS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghacs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghacs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhACS1 Gene Name: ACS-like protein Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The GhACS1 gene encodes an acyl-CoA synthetase which is essential for normal microsporogenesis in early anther development of cotton。 Real-time quantitative RT-PCR and northern blot analyses revealed that GhACS1 transcripts were predominantly accumulated in the developing anthers of cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhBZR3</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghbzr3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghbzr3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_A10G0312 Gene Symbol: GhBZR3 Gene Name: Genome: genome version is NBI v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCYP703A2</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcyp703a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcyp703a2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ghir D12G012350.1 Gene Symbol: GhCYP703A2 Gene Name: Genome: Gossypium hirsutum (TM-1) reference genome Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cytochrome P450 mono-oxygenase CYP703A2 plays a central role in sporopollenin formation and ms5ms6 fertility in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhFAD2-1A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a13g1850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a13g1850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A13G1850 Gene Symbol: GhFAD2-1A Gene Name: Genome: Cotton Functional Genomics Database (https://cottonfgd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhL1L1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d05g1686/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d05g1686/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D05G1686 Gene Symbol: GhL1L1 Gene Name: Leafy cotyledon1-like 1 Genome: Cotton Functional Genomics Database (https://cottonfgd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSSI2-A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhSSI2-A Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton GhSSI2 isoforms from the stearoyl acyl carrier protein fatty acid desaturase family regulate Verticillium wilt resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSSI2-B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhSSI2-B Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton GhSSI2 isoforms from the stearoyl acyl carrier protein fatty acid desaturase family regulate Verticillium wilt resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSSI2-C</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghssi2-c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhSSI2-C Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton GhSSI2 isoforms from the stearoyl acyl carrier protein fatty acid desaturase family regulate Verticillium wilt resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhWIN2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a07g036100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_a07g036100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_A07G036100 Gene Symbol: GhWIN2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The cotton GhWIN2 gene activates the cuticle biosynthesis pathway and influences the salicylic and jasmonic acid biosynthesis pathways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmACP</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/glyma.18g244300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/glycine-max/glyma.18g244300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.18g244300 Gene Symbol: GmACP Gene Name: acyl carrier protein Genome: Wm82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFAD2–1A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.10g278000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.10g278000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.10G278000 Gene Symbol: GmFAD2–1A Gene Name: Fatty Acid Desaturase 2 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Demonstration of highly efficient dual gRNA CRISPR/Cas9 editing of the homeologous GmFAD2–1A and GmFAD2–1B genes to yield a high oleic, low linoleic and α-linolenic acid phenotype in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFAD2–1B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.20g111000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.20g111000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.20G111000 Gene Symbol: GmFAD2–1B Gene Name: Fatty Acid Desaturase 2 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Demonstration of highly efficient dual gRNA CRISPR/Cas9 editing of the homeologous GmFAD2–1A and GmFAD2–1B genes to yield a high oleic, low linoleic and α-linolenic acid phenotype in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFATA1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gyma.18g167300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gyma.18g167300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gyma.18G167300 Gene Symbol: GmFATA1 Gene Name: acyl–acyl carrier protein thioesterase 1 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The acyl–acyl carrier protein thioesterases GmFATA1 and GmFATA2 are essential for fatty acid accumulation and growth in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFATA2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glyma.08g349200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glyma.08g349200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.08G349200 Gene Symbol: GmFATA2 Gene Name: acyl–acyl carrier protein thioesterase 2 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The acyl–acyl carrier protein thioesterases GmFATA1 and **GmFATA2 **are essential for fatty acid accumulation and growth in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPDCT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g213100.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g213100.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.08G213100.1 Gene Symbol: GmPDCT1 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Design of high-monounsaturated fatty acid soybean seed oil using GmPDCTs knockout via a CRISPR-Cas9 system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSACPD-A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.07g207200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.07g207200/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.07g207200 Gene Symbol: GmSACPD-A Gene Name: stearoyl-acyl carrier protein desaturase Genome: W82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSACPD-B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.02g138100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.02g138100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.02g138100 Gene Symbol: GmSACPD-B Gene Name: stearoyl-acyl carrier protein desaturase Genome: W82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSACPD-C</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.14g121400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.14g121400/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.14g121400 Gene Symbol: GmSACPD-C Gene Name: stearoyl-acyl carrier protein desaturase Genome: W82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSACPD-D</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.13g038600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.13g038600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.13g038600 Gene Symbol: GmSACPD-D Gene Name: stearoyl-acyl carrier protein desaturase Genome: W82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSACPD-E</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.13g038700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.13g038700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.13G038700 Gene Symbol: GmSACPD-E Gene Name: stearoyl-acyl carrier protein desaturase Genome: W82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWIN1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvWIN1 Gene Name: WAX INDUCER1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: WAX INDUCER1 (HvWIN1) transcription factor regulates free fatty acid biosynthetic genes to reinforce cuticle to resist Fusarium head blight in barley spikelets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeFAD7</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lefad7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lefad7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeFAD7 Gene Name: omega-3 fatty acid desaturase7 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Loss of Function of FATTY ACID DESATURASE7 (LeFAD7) in Tomato Enhances Basal Aphid Resistance in a Salicylate-Dependent Manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeGPAT</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/legpat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/legpat/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeGPAT Gene Name: glycerol-3-phosphate acyltransferase Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: A tomato (Solanum lycopersicum Mill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ms5</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ms5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ms5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ghir_A12G012140 Gene Symbol: Ms5 Gene Name: Genome: genome sequence of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ms6</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ms6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ms6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ghir_D12G012350 Gene Symbol: Ms6 Gene Name: Genome: genome sequence of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtFAD2–2a</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtFAD2–2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: We suggested that mutation of the seed-type NtFAD2–2 genes will not affect the fatty acid desaturation in tobacco leaves, because of the function redundancy of NtFAD2–1 genes in vegetative tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtFAD2–2b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtFAD2–2b Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: We suggested that mutation of the seed-type NtFAD2–2 genes will not affect the fatty acid desaturation in tobacco leaves, because of the function redundancy of NtFAD2–1 genes in vegetative tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLEA9</title>
      <link>/genes/brassica_napus/olea9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/brassica_napus/olea9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;BnaA09g39570D Gene Symbol: OLEA9 Gene Name: Genome: B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpFAD3-1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.6g056100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.6g056100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.6G056100 Gene Symbol: PpFAD3-1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: Peach fruit PpNAC1 activates PpFAD3-1 transcription to provide ω-3 fatty acids for the synthesis of short-chain flavor volatiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpNAC1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.4g187100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.4g187100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.4G187100 Gene Symbol: PpNAC1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor PpNAC1 and DNA demethylase PpDML1 synergistically regulate peach fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB144</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.07_1g012240.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.07_1g012240.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.07_1G012240.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB144 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 144 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB168</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.09_2g018520.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.09_2g018520.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.09_2G018520.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB168 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 168 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB24</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.02_4g016430.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.02_4g016430.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.02_4G016430.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB24 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 24 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaFAD3</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafad3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafad3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaFAD3 Gene Name: omega-3 fatty acid desaturase Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Temperature-dependent translational regulation of the ER omega-3 fatty acid desaturase gene in wheat root tips.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
