<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>plant defense signaling on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/plant-defense-signaling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in plant defense signaling on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/plant-defense-signaling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CaLOX2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g000103/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g000103/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana03g000103 Gene Symbol: CaLOX2 Gene Name: lipoxygenase 2 Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: Involvement of sweet pepper CaLOX2 in jasmonate-dependent induced defence against Western flower thrips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRab11A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csrab11a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csrab11a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRab11A Gene Name: Rab GTPase 11 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber (Cucumis sativus L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTCTP1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/cstctp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/cstctp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsTCTP1 Gene Name: translationally controlled tumor protein 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber (Cucumis sativus L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTCTP2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/cstctp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/cstctp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsTCTP2 Gene Name: translationally controlled tumor protein 2S Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber (Cucumis sativus L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FvLOX3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_6g34960/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_6g34960/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_6g34960 Gene Symbol: FvLOX3 Gene Name: lipoxygenase 3 Genome: Species: Fragaria vesca Functional Descriptions: FvMPK6 phosphorylates FvJAZ12 at the amino acid residues S179 and T183 adjacent to the PY residues, thereby attenuating its nuclear accumulation and relieving its repression for FvMYC2, which acts to control the expression of lipoxygenase 3 (FvLOX3), an important gene involved in JA biosynthesis and a diverse array of cellular metabolisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaJAZ1</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cotton_A_11862 Gene Symbol: GaJAZ1 Gene Name: Genome: Gossypium hirsutum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GbWRKY1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-barbadense/gbwrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-barbadense/gbwrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GbWRKY1 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Gossypium barbadense Functional Descriptions: Our data suggest that GbWRKY1 is a critical regulator mediating the plant defense-to-development transition during V.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSAMDC</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghsamdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghsamdc/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhSAMDC Gene Name: S-adenosylmethionine decarboxylase Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton S-adenosylmethionine decarboxylase(GhSAMDC)-mediated spermine biosynthesis is required for salicylic acid- and leucine-correlated signaling in the defense response to Verticillium dahliae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSPMS</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghspms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghspms/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhSPMS Gene Name: Spm synthase Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Cotton S-adenosylmethionine decarboxylase(GhSAMDC)-mediated spermine biosynthesis is required for salicylic acid- and leucine-correlated signaling in the defense response to Verticillium dahliae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhTINY2</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghtiny2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghtiny2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;GhD06G0642 Gene Symbol: GhTINY2 Gene Name: Genome: Cotton Functional Genomics Database Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Orchestration of plant development and defense by indirect crosstalk of salicylic acid and brassinosteorid signaling via transcription factor GhTINY2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmEDS1a</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmeds1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmeds1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.04g177700 Gene Symbol: GmEDS1a Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Silencing of GmEDS1a/b and GmPAD4 stopped accumulation of salicylic acid and increased the plant&amp;rsquo;s suceptibility to Pseudomonas syringae pv glycinea and soybean mosaic virus infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmEDS1b</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmeds1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmeds1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.06g187400 Gene Symbol: GmEDS1b Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Silencing of GmEDS1a/b and GmPAD4 stopped accumulation of salicylic acid and increased the plant&amp;rsquo;s suceptibility to Pseudomonas syringae pv glycinea and soybean mosaic virus infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPAD4</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmpad4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmpad4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.08g002100 Gene Symbol: GmPAD4 Gene Name: PHYTOALEXIN DEFICIENT 4 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Silencing of GmEDS1a/b and GmPAD4 stopped accumulation of salicylic acid and increased the plant&amp;rsquo;s suceptibility to Pseudomonas syringae pv glycinea and soybean mosaic virus infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeEix2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/leeix2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/leeix2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeEix2 Gene Name: receptor-like protein EIX2 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Endosomal signaling of the tomato leucine-rich repeat receptor-like protein LeEix2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LrABCF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LrABCF1 Gene Name: ATP-binding cassette transporter1 Genome: Species: Lilium regale Functional Descriptions: LrABCF1, a GCN-type ATP-binding cassette transporter from Lilium regale, is involved in defense responses against viral and fungal pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYC2</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/myc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/myc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g076930 Gene Symbol: MYC2 Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaZTL</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/niatv7_g26018-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/niatv7_g26018-/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: NIATv7_g26018 Gene Symbol: NaZTL Gene Name: ZEITLUPE Genome: NaDH (http://nadh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rpp17;OsERG1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g62430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g62430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g62430 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0841700 Gene Symbol: Rpp17 OsERG1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl-RGS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/solyc05g014160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/solyc05g014160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc05g014160 Gene Symbol: Sl-RGS1 Gene Name: G protein signaling 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: RGS1 negatively regulates disease resistance and is required for glucose-enhanced defense under low light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlWRKY75</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g015850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g015850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc05g015850 Gene Symbol: SlWRKY75 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor75 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Here, we characterized tomato (Solanum lycopersicum) SlWRKY75, which promotes defenses against P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaADF4</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taadf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/taadf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaADF4 Gene Name: actin-depolymerizing factor 4 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaADF4, an actin-depolymerizing factor from wheat, is required for resistance to the stripe rust pathogen Puccinia striiformis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSnRK2.4</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g381100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs3a02g381100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS3A02G381100 Gene Symbol: TaSnRK2.4 Gene Name: Triticum aestivum SNF1-type serine-threonine protein kinase Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: TaSnRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAPX1;apx3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1apx3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1apx3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb013080 Gene Symbol: ZmAPX1 apx3 Gene Name: ascorbate peroxidase 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
