<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sucrose on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>/tags/sucrose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sucrose on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/sucrose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABF2</title>
      <link>/genes/citrus_sinensis/abf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrus_sinensis/abf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g23480 Gene Symbol: ABF2 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A model was proposed to illustrate how ABF2 mediates the ABA signalling involved in sucrose transport, chlorophyll degradation, auxin homoeostasis, carotenoid and ABA biosynthesis, and cell wall metabolism during citrus fruit development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrOG1A</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/braa08002322/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/braa08002322/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraA08002322 Gene Symbol: BrOG1A Gene Name: Orphan gene 1 Genome: B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrOG1B</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/brasca000221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-rapa/brasca000221/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraSca000221 Gene Symbol: BrOG1B Gene Name: Orphan gene 2 Genome: B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitAMT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis-x-poncirus-trifoliata/citamt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis-x-poncirus-trifoliata/citamt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CitAMT1 Gene Name: ammonium transporter1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis x Poncirus trifoliata Functional Descriptions: Ammonium transport and CitAMT1 expression are regulated by N in Citrus plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitSUS5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citsus5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citsus5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CitSUS5 Gene Name: sucrose synthase 5 Genome: Citrus Genome Database Species: Citrus reticulata Functional Descriptions: Expression analyses and functional characterizations of CitSUS5 and CitSWEET6 support their proposed role in regulating fructose and glucose levels, hexose to sucrose ratio, and sucrose synthase cleavage activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitSWEET6</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citsweet6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citsweet6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CitSWEET6 Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter 6 Genome: Citrus Genome Database Species: Citrus reticulata Functional Descriptions: Expression analyses and functional characterizations of CitSUS5 and CitSWEET6 support their proposed role in regulating fructose and glucose levels, hexose to sucrose ratio, and sucrose synthase cleavage activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitZAT5</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-reticulata/citzat5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-reticulata/citzat5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CitZAT5 Gene Name: ZINC FINGER OF ARABIDOPSIS THALIANA Genome: Citrus Genome Database Species: Citrus reticulata Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor CitZAT5 modifies sugar accumulation and hexose proportion in citrus fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClINV</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clinv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clinv/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C10G201810 Gene Symbol: ClINV Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Transcriptome analysis showed that the invertase gene ClINV was the only gene involved in sucrose metabolism that was upregulated in mutant flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClNAC68</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C03G059250 Gene Symbol: ClNAC68 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: The NAC transcription factor ClNAC68 positively regulates sugar content and seed development in watermelon by repressing ClINV and ClGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClSnRK2.3</title>
      <link>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C02G038540 Gene Symbol: ClSnRK2.3 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClSnRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClVST1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c02g031010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c02g031010/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C02G031010 Gene Symbol: ClVST1 Gene Name: vacuolar sugar transporter Genome: watermelon genome database Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Report a novel vacuolar sugar transporter (ClVST1) identified through map-based cloning and association study, whose expression in fruit phloem is associated with accumulation of sucrose (Suc) in watermelon fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmERFI-2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/melo3c002624/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/melo3c002624/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MELO3C002624 Gene Symbol: CmERFI-2 Gene Name: ethylene response factor I-2 Genome: melon genome database (http://cucurbitgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmFTL2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmftl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/chrysanthemum-morifolium/cmftl2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmFTL2 Gene Name: flowering locus T-like 2 Genome: Species: Chrysanthemum morifolium Functional Descriptions: CmFTL2 is involved in the photoperiod- and sucrose-mediated control of flowering time in chrysanthemum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmMYB44</title>
      <link>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmmyb44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/cucumis_melo/cmmyb44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MELO3C016789 Gene Symbol: CmMYB44 Gene Name: MYB44 transcription factor Genome: Melon (DHL92) v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmTST2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/cmtst2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-melo/cmtst2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CmTST2 Gene Name: tonoplast sugar transporter2 Genome: Species: Cucumis melo Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of the tonoplast sugar transporter CmTST2 in melon fruit increases sugar accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS1 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS2 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS3 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUS3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssus3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssus3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSUS3 Gene Name: Sucrose Synthase 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Antisense expression of CsSUS3 clearly reduced cucumber tolerance to hypoxic stress induced by flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUS4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g322500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g322500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G322500 Gene Symbol: CsSUS4 Gene Name: Sucrose Synthase 4 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Down-Regulating Cucumber Sucrose Synthase 4 (CsSUS4) Suppresses the Growth and Development of Flowers and Fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSUT1 Gene Name: Sucrose Transporter 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the Sucrose Transporter CsSUT1 Causes Male Sterility by Altering Carbohydrate Supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D1;RGA1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g26890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g26890/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g26890 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0333200 Gene Symbol: D1 RGA1 LW5 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D53</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g01330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g01330/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g01330 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0104300 ,Os11g0104350 Gene Symbol: D53 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUS1;FLR1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g21540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g21540/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g21540 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0333200 Gene Symbol: DRUS1 FLR1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ereb17</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/ereb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/ereb17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb194220 Gene Symbol: Ereb17 Gene Name: AP2-EREBP-transcription factor 17 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGAMYB</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fagamyb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fagamyb/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGAMYB Gene Name: MYB transcription factor Genome: Species: Fragaria vesca Functional Descriptions: Central role of FaGAMYB in the transition of the strawberry receptacle from development to ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLO22</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g08180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g08180/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g08180 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0179000 Gene Symbol: FLO22 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FvMAPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_7g15060/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-vesca/fvh4_7g15060/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_7g15060 Gene Symbol: FvMAPK3 Gene Name: MITOGEN-ACTIVATED PROTEIN KINASE 3 Genome: Fragaria vesca ID (v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GF14f;OsGF14f</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g50290/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g50290/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g50290 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0710800 Gene Symbol: GF14f OsGF14f Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK84</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d10g2029/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d10g2029/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D10G2029 Gene Symbol: GhCPK84 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Comparative phosphoproteomic analysis reveals that phosphorylation of sucrose synthase GhSUS2 by Ca2+-dependent protein kinases GhCPK84/GhCPK93 affects cotton fiber development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCPK93</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d12g2743/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d12g2743/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D12G2743 Gene Symbol: GhCPK93 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Comparative phosphoproteomic analysis reveals that phosphorylation of sucrose synthase GhSUS2 by Ca2+-dependent protein kinases GhCPK84/GhCPK93 affects cotton fiber development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMYB212</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.007g350500.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.007g350500.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gorai.007G350500.1 Gene Symbol: GhMYB212 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 212 Genome: Phytozome v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSCP2D</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghscp2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghscp2d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D06G0145 Gene Symbol: GhSCP2D Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSUS2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d08g1309/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gh_d08g1309/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gh_D08G1309 Gene Symbol: GhSUS2 Gene Name: sucrose synthase 2 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Comparative phosphoproteomic analysis reveals that phosphorylation of sucrose synthase GhSUS2 by Ca2+-dependent protein kinases GhCPK84/93 affects cotton fiber development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSWEET10D</title>
      <link>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsweet10d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghsweet10d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D12G1898 Gene Symbol: GhSWEET10D Gene Name: Genome: genomes of G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhSWEET12</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.005g195100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/gorai.005g195100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gorai.005G195100 Gene Symbol: GhSWEET12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: RNA-seq and protein−DNA binding assays revealed that GhMYB212 was closely linked to the pathways of sucrose and starch transportation and metabolism, directly controling the expression of a sucrose transporter gene GhSWEET12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmHSP17.9</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmhsp17.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmhsp17.9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.17G045800 Gene Symbol: GmHSP17.9 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: A small heat shock protein, GmHSP17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmNOD100;GmSS1</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmnod100gmss1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmnod100gmss1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.13G114000 Gene Symbol: GmNOD100 GmSS1 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmNOD100, a sucrose synthase in soybean nodules which was also preferentially expressed in the infected zone of nodules, similar to GmHSP17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSWEET10b</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmsweet10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmsweet10b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.08G183500 Gene Symbol: GmSWEET10b Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Simultaneous changes in seed size, oil content and protein content driven by selection of SWEET homologues during soybean domestication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSWEET6</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/gmsweet6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/gmsweet6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.04G198600 Gene Symbol: GmSWEET6 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmSWEET6, was functionally characterised in soybean, and its role in AM symbiosis was investigated via transgenic plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmWNK1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmwnk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmwnk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmWNK1 Gene Name: WNK kinase homolog1 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The soybean root-specific protein kinase GmWNK1 regulates stress-responsive ABA signaling on the root system architecture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HbSUT3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hevea-brasiliensis/hbsut3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hevea-brasiliensis/hbsut3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HbSUT3 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 3 Genome: Species: Hevea brasiliensis Functional Descriptions: HbSUT3 encodes a functional sucrose transporter that exhibits high sucrose affinity with a Km value of 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g075200.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g075200.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU4Hr1G075200.3 Gene Symbol: HvSUT1 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the sucrose transporters HvSUT1 and HvSUT2 affects sucrose homeostasis along its delivery path in barley grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSUT2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu5hr1g000010.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu5hr1g000010.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU5Hr1G000010.1 Gene Symbol: HvSUT2 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 2 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the sucrose transporters HvSUT1 and HvSUT2 affects sucrose homeostasis along its delivery path in barley grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSWEET11b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g054710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g054710/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU7Hr1G054710 Gene Symbol: HvSWEET11b Gene Name: Sugars Will Eventually be Exported Transporter 11 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A radiotracer assay revealed that expressing HvSWEET11b in African clawed frog (Xenopus laevis) oocytes facilitated the bidirectional transfer of not only just sucrose and glucose, but also cytokinin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbSnRK1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibsnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibsnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbSnRK1 Gene Name: sucrose non-fermenting-1-related protein kinase-1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: These findings indicate that IbSnRK1 improves starch content and quality through systematical up-regulation of the genes and the increase in key enzyme activities involved in starch biosynthesis pathway in transgenic sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVAN6;Mei025</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/invan6mei025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/invan6mei025/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb230860 Gene Symbol: INVAN6 Mei025 Gene Name: INVERTASE ALKALINE NEUTRAL 6 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KASI</title>
      <link>/genes/glycine_max/kasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/glycine_max/kasi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.08G084300 Gene Symbol: KASI Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: KASI is a core fatty acid synthesis enzyme that is involved in the conversion of sucrose into oil in developing seeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAT-2A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS6A02G392400 Gene Symbol: KAT-2A Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAT-2B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS6B02G432600 Gene Symbol: KAT-2B Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAT-2D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/kat-2d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS6D02G493900LC Gene Symbol: KAT-2D Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeFRK2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lefrk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lefrk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeFRK2 Gene Name: fructokinase2 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: LeFRK2 is required for phloem and xylem differentiation and the transport of both sugar and water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lesut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/lesut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LeSUT1 Gene Name: sucrose transport protein 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Sucrose transporter LeSUT1 and LeSUT2 inhibition affects tomato fruit development in different ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdbHLH3-27</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbhlh3-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdbhlh3-27/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD00G1130200 Gene Symbol: MdbHLH3-27 Gene Name: Malus domestica basic helix–loop–helix 3 Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdCBF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md07g1262900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md07g1262900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD07G1262900 Gene Symbol: MdCBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The MdCBF1/MdCBF2-MdTST1/MdTST2 module regulates sugar accumulation in response to low temperature in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdCBF2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1196100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1196100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD01G1196100 Gene Symbol: MdCBF2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The MdCBF1/MdCBF2-MdTST1/MdTST2 module regulates sugar accumulation in response to low temperature in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdcyMDH1</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdcymdh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdcymdh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD13G1214000 Gene Symbol: MdcyMDH1 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdFRK2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000323311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000323311/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000323311 Gene Symbol: MdFRK2 Gene Name: fructokinase 2 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Increased activity of MdFRK2, a high-affinity fructokinase, leads to upregulation of sorbitol metabolism and downregulation of sucrose metabolism in apple leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdHT2.2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdht2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdht2.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD15G1193400/MDP0000154362 Gene Symbol: MdHT2.2 Gene Name: apple hexose transporter 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdJAZ18</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000757701/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000757701/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000757701 Gene Symbol: MdJAZ18 Gene Name: jasmonate ZIM-domain protein 18 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdNB-ARC</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdnb-arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdnb-arc/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD09G1272500 Gene Symbol: MdNB-ARC Gene Name: Genome: Malus x domestica Whole Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSnRK1.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000191788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000191788/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000191788 Gene Symbol: MdSnRK1.1 Gene Name: SNF1-related protein kinase 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: An Apple Protein Kinase MdSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSPSB2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdspsb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdspsb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD10G1002500 Gene Symbol: MdSPSB2 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSPSC2</title>
      <link>/genes/malus_domestica/mdspsc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/malus_domestica/mdspsc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD10G1002300 Gene Symbol: MdSPSC2 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSUT4.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md08g1209900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md08g1209900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD08G1209900 Gene Symbol: MdSUT4.1 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 4 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The sucrose transporter MdSUT4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSWEET9b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsweet9b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdsweet9b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdSWEET9b Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Abscisic acid and regulation of the sugar transporter gene MdSWEET9b promote apple sugar accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdTST1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md06g1005100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md06g1005100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD06G1005100 Gene Symbol: MdTST1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The MdCBF1/MdCBF2-MdTST1/MdTST2 module regulates sugar accumulation in response to low temperature in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdTST2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md10g1142100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md10g1142100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD10G1142100 Gene Symbol: MdTST2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The MdCBF1/MdCBF2-MdTST1/MdTST2 module regulates sugar accumulation in response to low temperature in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mn1;CWIN2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/mn1cwin2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/mn1cwin2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb083790 Gene Symbol: Mn1 CWIN2 Gene Name: miniature seed1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOC2;FBP1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g64660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g64660/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g64660 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0866400 Gene Symbol: MOC2 FBP1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsSPSA</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msspsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msspsa/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MsSPSA Gene Name: sucrose phosphate synthase Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Nodule-enhanced expression of a sucrose phosphate synthase gene member (MsSPSA) has a role in carbon and nitrogen metabolism in the nodules of alfalfa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRR;CRCT</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g51690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g51690/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g51690 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0595300 Gene Symbol: NRR CRCT Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OeMST2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/olea-europaea/oemst2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/olea-europaea/oemst2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: OeMST2 Gene Name: monosaccharide transporter 2 Genome: Species: Olea europaea Functional Descriptions: OeMST2 Encodes a Monosaccharide Transporter Expressed throughout Olive Fruit Maturation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Os11N3;OsSWEET14</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g31190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os11g31190/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os11g31190 RAPdb gene ID: Os11g0508600 Gene Symbol: Os11N3 OsSWEET14 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Os8N3;xa13</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g42350/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g42350/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g42350 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0535200 Gene Symbol: Os8N3 xa13 OsSWEET11 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsAKT2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g35410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g35410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g35410 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0428700 Gene Symbol: OsAKT2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCam1-1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g20370/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g20370/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g20370 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0319300 Gene Symbol: OsCam1-1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCCA1;Nhd1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g06110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g06110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g06110 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0157600 Gene Symbol: OsCCA1 Nhd1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OscFBP2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g36270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g36270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g36270 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0438600 Gene Symbol: OscFBP2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCKT1;OHK5</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g50480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g50480/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g50480 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0738400 Gene Symbol: OsCKT1 OHK5 OsHk6 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsCPK17</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g06740/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g06740/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g06740 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0161600 Gene Symbol: OsCPK17 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsDOF11</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g47810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g47810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g47810 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0707200 Gene Symbol: OsDOF11 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsERF2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g08340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g08340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g08340 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0181700 Gene Symbol: OsERF2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGCS1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g18730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g18730/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g18730 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0269500 Gene Symbol: OsGCS1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsGI</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g08700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g08700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g08700 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0182600 Gene Symbol: OsGI Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsHAK1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g32920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g32920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g32920 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0401700 Gene Symbol: OsHAK1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsIDD2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os01g09850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os01g09850 RAPdb gene ID: Os01g0195000 ,Os01g0195066 Gene Symbol: OsIDD2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsINV2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g45290/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g45290/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g45290 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0535600 Gene Symbol: OsINV2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSINV3;OsVIN2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g01590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g01590/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g01590 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0106100 Gene Symbol: OSINV3 OsVIN2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPIP1;2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g47220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g47220/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g47220 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0559700 Gene Symbol: OsPIP1 2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsPK3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g58110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os04g58110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os04g58110 RAPdb gene ID: Os04g0677500 Gene Symbol: OsPK3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsrbohB;Osrboh7</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g26660/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g26660 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0438000 Gene Symbol: OsrbohB Osrboh7 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSAC1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g02520/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g02520/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g02520 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0116300 Gene Symbol: OsSAC1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSAUR33</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g35110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g35110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g35110 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0452500 Gene Symbol: OsSAUR33 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSGL</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g04130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g04130/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g04130 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0134200 Gene Symbol: OsSGL Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g07480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g07480/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g07480 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0170900 Gene Symbol: OsSUT1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSWEET11b</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g32992/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g32992/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g32992 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0508250 Gene Symbol: OsSWEET11b Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsSWEET15</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g30910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g30910/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g30910 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0513100 Gene Symbol: OsSWEET15 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTMT1;OsTST1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g39440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g39440/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g39440 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0539900 Gene Symbol: OsTMT1 OsTST1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTPP7;AG1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g20390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g20390/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g20390 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0369400 Gene Symbol: OsTPP7 AG1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTRE1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g37660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g37660/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g37660 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0521000 Gene Symbol: OsTRE1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsTSD2;OsQUA2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g51860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g51860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g51860 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0755000 Gene Symbol: OsTSD2 OsQUA2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsXDH;OsSAC3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g31550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g31550/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g31550 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0429800 Gene Symbol: OsXDH OsSAC3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PagGS1;2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-alba-p.-glandulosa/paggs12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/populus-alba-p.-glandulosa/paggs12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PagGS1;2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus alba × P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrbZIP15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbrbzip15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbrbzip15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbrbZIP15 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus bretschneideri Functional Descriptions: PbrbZIP15, was characterized from pear genome through the combined analyses of metabolite and transcriptome data followed by experimental validation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLS2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g15840/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g15840/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g15840 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0265100 Gene Symbol: PLS2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpINH1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.5g112600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.5g112600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.5G112600 Gene Symbol: PpINH1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: PpINH1, an invertase inhibitor, interacts with vacuolar invertase PpVIN2 in regulating the chilling tolerance of peach fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpSnRK1βγ</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.6g323700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/prupe.6g323700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Prupe.6G323700 Gene Symbol: PpSnRK1βγ Gene Name: sucrose non-fermenting 1 related kinase Genome: reference peach genome (release version 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpVIN2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppvin2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/prunus-persica/ppvin2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PpVIN2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Prunus persica Functional Descriptions: PpINH1, an invertase inhibitor, interacts with vacuolar invertase PpVIN2 in regulating the chilling tolerance of peach fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuWRKY31</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/puwrky31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/puwrky31/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuWRKY31 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 31 Genome: Species: Pyrus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: The expression of the transcription factor PuWRKY31 was higher in BNG fruit than in NG fruit, and was induced by sucrose treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhSUC2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsuc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsuc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhSUC2 Gene Name: sucrose proton symporter 2 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Regulation of RhSUC2, a sucrose transporter, is correlated with the light control of bud burst in Rosa sp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSUS3;SUS3</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42490/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42490/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g42490 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0616800 Gene Symbol: RSUS3 SUS3 OsSUS3 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAPK1;OsSAPK1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g27280/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os03g27280/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os03g27280 RAPdb gene ID: Os03g0390200 Gene Symbol: SAPK1 OsSAPK1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAPK2;OsSAPK2</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g42940/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g42940 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0622000 Gene Symbol: SAPK2 OsSAPK2 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SbSAI-2</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sbsai-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/sorghum-bicolor/sbsai-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SbSAI-2 Gene Name: soluble acid invertase 2 Genome: Species: Sorghum bicolor Functional Descriptions: The sorghum soluble acid invertase gene SbSAI-2 was cloned and the function verified in Pichia pastoris and rice, showing the SbSAI-2 affects composition and content of sugar in stem juice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sh1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/sh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/sh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb374090 Gene Symbol: Sh1 Gene Name: shrunken1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/saccharum-hybrid/shsut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/saccharum-hybrid/shsut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: ShSUT1 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 1 Genome: Species: Saccharum hybrid Functional Descriptions: Here we present a functional analysis of the SUT ShSUT1 from sugarcane, an important crop species grown for its ability to accumulate high amounts of sucrose in the stem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlARF10</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc11g069500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc11g069500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc11g069500 Gene Symbol: SlARF10 Gene Name: auxin response factor 10 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlARF10, an auxin response factor, is involved in chlorophyll and sugar accumulation during tomato fruit development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlJUL</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/sljul/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc08g067180.3.1 Gene Symbol: SlJUL Gene Name: Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSUS4</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slsus4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slsus4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlSUS4 Gene Name: sucrose synthase isoform 4 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Comparison of a novel tomato sucrose synthase, SlSUS4, with previously described SlSUS isoforms reveals distinct sequence features and differential expression patterns in association with stem maturation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSUT4</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slsut4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_lycopersicum/slsut4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Solyc04g076960.2.1 Gene Symbol: SlSUT4 Gene Name: Sucrose transporter 4 Genome: Tomato Genome version SL4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSWEET15</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g074530/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc09g074530/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc09g074530 Gene Symbol: SlSWEET15 Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter 15 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Transporter SlSWEET15 unloads sucrose from phloem and seed coat for fruit and seed development in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SnRK1A;OsSnRK1a</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g45420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os05g45420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os05g45420 RAPdb gene ID: Os05g0530500 Gene Symbol: SnRK1A OsSnRK1a OsSnRK1A1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StABF1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StABF1 Gene Name: ABRE binding factor1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StABF1, a stress-responsive bZIP transcription factor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPP2Ac2b</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpp2ac2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpp2ac2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPP2Ac2b Gene Name: protein phosphatase 2A catalytic subunit Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The protein phosphatase 2A catalytic subunit StPP2Ac2b is involved in the control of potato tuber sprouting and source–sink balance in tubers and sprouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSUT1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanaceae-tuberosum/stsut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanaceae-tuberosum/stsut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StSUT1 Gene Name: sucrose transport protein1 Genome: Species: Solanaceae tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The Potato Sucrose Transporter StSUT1 Interacts with a DRM-Associated Protein Disulfide Isomerase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSWEET11</title>
      <link>/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsweet11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsweet11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: StSWEET11 Gene Name: Genome: Potato Genome Sequencing Consortium website (http://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTINY3</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G035540.1 Gene Symbol: StTINY3 Gene Name: CBF/DREB transcription factor3 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor StTINY3 enhances cold-induced sweetening resistance by coordinating starch resynthesis and sucrose hydrolysis in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWEET12c</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g024260/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc05g024260/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc05g024260 Gene Symbol: SWEET12c Gene Name: Sugars Will Eventually be Exported Transporter Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Further analyses suggested that HY5 represses the accumulation of sugar in tomato fruit by activating Sugars Will Eventually be Exported Transporter (SWEET12c) expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sxd1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb237270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb237270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb237270 Gene Symbol: sxd1 Gene Name: sucrose export defective1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sxd1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/sxd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/sxd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb237270 Gene Symbol: Sxd1 Gene Name: sucrose export defective1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaFROG</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4A02G201900 Gene Symbol: TaFROG Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaFROG-4B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog-4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog-4b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4B02G106100 Gene Symbol: TaFROG-4B Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaFROG-4D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog-4d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tafrog-4d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4D02G102800 Gene Symbol: TaFROG-4D Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSnRK2.10-4A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4a02g235600.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4a02g235600.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS4A02G235600.2 Gene Symbol: TaSnRK2.10-4A Gene Name: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 (SnRK2) acts as a signaling hub in the response to drought stress, but whether SnRK2 helps plants cope with water deficit via other mechanisms is largely unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSnRK2.10-4B</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4b02g079300.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4b02g079300.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS4B02G079300.1 Gene Symbol: TaSnRK2.10-4B Gene Name: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 (SnRK2) acts as a signaling hub in the response to drought stress, but whether SnRK2 helps plants cope with water deficit via other mechanisms is largely unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSnRK2.10-4D</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4d02g078100.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/traescs4d02g078100.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS4D02G078100.2 Gene Symbol: TaSnRK2.10-4D Gene Name: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Sucrose non-fermenting 1-related protein kinase 2 (SnRK2) acts as a signaling hub in the response to drought stress, but whether SnRK2 helps plants cope with water deficit via other mechanisms is largely unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSTP3</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tastp3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tastp3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS2B02G282400 Gene Symbol: TaSTP3 Gene Name: Sugar Transport Protein 3 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaTPP-7A</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tatpp-7a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tatpp-7a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7A03G0422300 Gene Symbol: TaTPP-7A Gene Name: Trehalose-phosphatase Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWRKY19</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky19/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS2D02G190500 Gene Symbol: TaWRKY19 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor19 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWRKY61</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky61/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS5D02G116100 Gene Symbol: TaWRKY61 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaWRKY82</title>
      <link>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky82/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/triticum_aestivum/tawrky82/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS7A02G294800 Gene Symbol: TaWRKY82 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tdy1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb297040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb297040/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb297040 Gene Symbol: Tdy1 Gene Name: tie-dyed1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tdy2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb259620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb259620/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb259620 Gene Symbol: tdy2 Gene Name: tie-dyed2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvSnRK1.1</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_00025806001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vit_00025806001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VIT_00025806001 Gene Symbol: VvSnRK1.1 Gene Name: SNF1-related protein kinase catalytic subunit alpha KIN10 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: VvTOR interacts with VvSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvTOR</title>
      <link>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvtor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvtor/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvTOR Gene Name: serine/threonine-protein kinase TOR Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: VvTOR interacts with VvSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTG1;OsOTUB1</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g42540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os08g42540/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os08g42540 RAPdb gene ID: Os08g0537800 Gene Symbol: WTG1 OsOTUB1 GWC1 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xa25;OsSWEET13</title>
      <link>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os12g29220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os12g29220/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os12g29220 RAPdb gene ID: Os12g0476200 Gene Symbol: Xa25 OsSWEET13 Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zm00001eb257680</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257680/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb257680/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb257680 Gene Symbol: Zm00001eb257680 Gene Name: sucrose non-fermenting 1 kinase interactor-like protein Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmABI19;ZmAFL2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmabi19zmafl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmabi19zmafl2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb361390 Gene Symbol: ZmABI19 ZmAFL2 Gene Name: ABI3-VP1-transcription factor 19 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmbZIP113;bzip113</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip113bzip113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmbzip113bzip113/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb431760 Gene Symbol: ZmbZIP113 bzip113 Gene Name: bZIP-transcription factor 113 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmCESA5;ENB1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmcesa5enb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmcesa5enb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb061800 Gene Symbol: ZmCESA5 ENB1 Gene Name: cellulose synthase5 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNAC128;ZmNAC34</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnac128zmnac34nactf128nrp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnac128zmnac34nactf128nrp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb126890 Gene Symbol: ZmNAC128 ZmNAC34 nactf128 nrp1 Gene Name: no-apical-meristem-related protein1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmNAC130;nactf130</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmnac130nactf130nac130nac4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmnac130nactf130nac130nac4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb334180 Gene Symbol: ZmNAC130 nactf130 nac130 nac4 Gene Name: NAC-transcription factor 130 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmRAFS;ZmRS</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmrafszmrsrafs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmrafszmrsrafs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb122980 Gene Symbol: ZmRAFS ZmRS rafs1 Gene Name: raffinose synthase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSnRK1a2;ZmSnRK1.2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsnrk1a2zmsnrk1.2zmsnrk1.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsnrk1a2zmsnrk1.2zmsnrk1.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb094400 Gene Symbol: ZmSnRK1a2 ZmSnRK1.2 ZmSnRK1.3 Gene Name: SNF1-related kinase alpha1-like2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSTK1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb374240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb374240/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb374240 Gene Symbol: ZmSTK1 Gene Name: serine threonine kinase1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSTK2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb192750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb192750/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb192750 Gene Symbol: ZmSTK2|stk3 Gene Name: serine-threonine kinase3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSTP3;ZmSTP8</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmstp3zmstp8stp12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmstp3zmstp8stp12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb043150 Gene Symbol: ZmSTP3 ZmSTP8 stp12 Gene Name: sugar transport protein12 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSUGCAR1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb304390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zm00001eb304390/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb304390 Gene Symbol: ZmSUGCAR1|ZmNPF7.9|MN2 Gene Name: Sucrose and Glucose Carrier1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSUT1;sut1</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut1sut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut1sut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb005460 Gene Symbol: ZmSUT1 sut1 Gene Name: sucrose transporter1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSut2;sut2</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut2sut2sut4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut2sut2sut4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb133930 Gene Symbol: ZmSut2 sut2 sut4 Gene Name: sucrose transporter2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSUT4</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsut4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb259340 Gene Symbol: ZmSUT4 Gene Name: sucrose transporter4 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET11;sweet11a</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet11sweet11a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet11sweet11a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb036880 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET11 sweet11a Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter11 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET13b;ZmSWEET18</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet13bzmsweet18zmsweet19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet13bzmsweet18zmsweet19/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb408900 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET13b ZmSWEET18 ZmSWEET19 Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter13b Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET14a;ZmSWEET3</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet14azmsweet3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet14azmsweet3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb113080 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET14a ZmSWEET3 Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter14a Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET15a;ZmSWEET10</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet15azmsweet10zmsweet9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet15azmsweet10zmsweet9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb180830 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET15a ZmSWEET10 ZmSWEET9 Gene Name: Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET3a;ZmSWEET15</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet3azmsweet15zmsweet16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet3azmsweet15zmsweet16/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb350590 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET3a ZmSWEET15 ZmSWEET16 Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter3a Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSWEET4c</title>
      <link>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet4c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/genes/zea_mays/zmsweet4c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb236810 Gene Symbol: ZmSWEET4c Gene Name: sugars will eventually be exported transporter4c Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
